<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Feat3 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/feat3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Feat3 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/feat3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: The Nest Rooftop Bar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-the-nest-rooftop-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-the-nest-rooftop-bar/</guid>
      <description>Image: MTotoe&#xA;The Nest is a welcome addition to London’s plethora of rooftop bars and is located just a short walk from Oxford Circus station. The bar sits on the 16th floor of the Treehouse Hotel which opened just under a year ago. It’s a quirky, green haven filled with wooden furniture and a wraparound terrace, offering 360-degree views of the city.&#xA;Whilst the food menu isn&amp;rsquo;t particularly extensive, think small plates and light snacks, they do have a great selection of cocktails to make up for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London’s best indoor green spaces to escape the winter blues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</guid>
      <description>When the winter chill sets in and the London skies are often grey and rainy, indoor green spaces offer the perfect escape. From towering tropical plants to lush Victorian conservatories, here are some of the most remarkable indoor gardens to visit in London, providing a serene environment for relaxation and inspiration, no matter the weather.&#xA;Barbican Conservatory Barbican Conservatory, Barbican Centre. © MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Step into a hidden world of exotic plants and trees at the Barbican Conservatory, a tropical oasis nestled within the iconic Barbican Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in October 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</guid>
      <description>October has arrived and London is back, and there are heaps of great events on. With Halloween events back in full swing, Black History Month and some of the best in arts and culture including Southbank’s London Literature Festival and Frieze London, it’s shaping up to be a big one!&#xA;Here are some of our favourite things you can do in the city this October.&#xA;Affordable Art Fair Battersea Autumn When: 20 – 23 October 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London this weekend: 8-10 March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this weekend: 8 –10 March 2024.&#xA;New York City Ballet (NYCB)&#xA;New York City Ballet, founded in 1948 by George Balanchine and Lincoln Kirstein, is renowned for its blend of contemporary creations and classic choreographies. Their upcoming performance in the UK presents a rare opportunity to witness the company&amp;rsquo;s world-class talent. The repertoire includes Justin Peck&amp;rsquo;s Rotunda, featuring a commissioned score by Nico Muhly, Duo Concertant by Balanchine, Pam Tanowitz&amp;rsquo;s Gustave le Gray No.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
