<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Virusfeat on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/virusfeat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Virusfeat on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/virusfeat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Dr Zara Benjamin-Laing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-dr-zara-benjamin-laing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-dr-zara-benjamin-laing/</guid>
      <description>We had a chat with Dr Zara to discover what a day in the life at Birmingham hospital amid the coronavirus pandemic.&#xA;Key workers have been working tirelessly on the front line throughout our nation’s battle against coronavirus. We caught up with NHS doctor, Zara Benjamin-Laing, to discover how day-to-day life has changed at the hospital she works at amid the current pandemic.&#xA;Image: Zara Benjamin-Laing&#xA;Dr Zara Benjamin-Laing is a Senior House Officer (SHO) currently working in Birmingham.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working from home: love it or hate it, it’s here to stay, so let’s make it work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/working-from-home-love-it-or-hate-it-its-here-to-stay-so-lets-make-it-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/working-from-home-love-it-or-hate-it-its-here-to-stay-so-lets-make-it-work/</guid>
      <description>I had never been one for working from home before the lockdown, claiming that my job wasn’t really do-able from home (I can now safely say that’s not the case). But now that I’ve been forced to, I’m quite enjoying working from home and I hope that in some capacity it will stick. Here are some of the things that I’ve found useful for making it work (excuse the pun).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London at home: theatre shows available to stream</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/theatre-shows-available-to-stream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/theatre-shows-available-to-stream/</guid>
      <description>The entertainment industry might be on hold for the moment, but there’s still ways to bring the theatre to your living room. With our guide, you can still enjoy a range of shows while we’re all still in lockdown.&#xA;Shakespeare’s Globe Image: Shakespeare’s Globe&#xA;Between the years of 1592-93, The Globe was closed due to an outbreak of the plague. Although The Globe is currently closed again, fortunately this time around, you can still watch a selection of Shakespeare’s plays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual dating during lockdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/love-lockdown-virtual-dating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/love-lockdown-virtual-dating/</guid>
      <description>With the devastating news that Love Island 2020 has been cancelled due to COVID-19, FLO London is here to help fill that void and give you some tips for a thriving virtual dating life. Who would have thought that hit Netflix shows Love is Blind and Too Hot to Handle would somehow become a reality for single people around the world? Is it possible to form a ‘deep connection’ with someone you’ve never met before?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
