<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London8 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/london8/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London8 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/london8/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Artist’s Garden: the transformation of Temple Station&#39;s roof terrace</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-transformation-of-temple-stations-roof-terrace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-transformation-of-temple-stations-roof-terrace/</guid>
      <description>Holly Hendry&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Slackwater&amp;rsquo; is the latest art installation to appear in the Artist&amp;rsquo;s Garden on the roof of Temple Station.&#xA;Image: Holly Hendry&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Slackwater&amp;rsquo; Artist Roof Garden. July 2023. © MTotoe&#xA;Holly Hendry&amp;rsquo;s art installation, Slackwater, takes centre stage in the Artist&amp;rsquo;s Garden by Temple tube station. The installation features a maze of intricately entangled tubes, constructed with industrial-scale ducting, electricity spools, and inflated boat fenders. Representing the area&amp;rsquo;s watery history and the abstract rhythms of the Thames and the human body, this large-scale sculpture will be on display on the rooftop site until September 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 26 June – 2 July 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-26-june-2-july-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-26-june-2-july-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 26 June – 2 July 2023.&#xA;Explore London Chelsea &amp;amp; Kensington Festival 2023&#xA;Kensington and Chelsea Festival is returning for its third year this week. Taking place from 1 July - 31 August 2023. The festival will showcase a wide range of live art performances in various venues and outdoor spaces, featuring established artists and emerging talent. It offers a diverse cultural program including theatre, circus, opera, dance, music, outdoor arts, family shows, talks, and more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
