<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Emma on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/emma/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Emma on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/emma/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>London at home: theatre shows available to stream</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/theatre-shows-available-to-stream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/theatre-shows-available-to-stream/</guid>
      <description>The entertainment industry might be on hold for the moment, but there’s still ways to bring the theatre to your living room. With our guide, you can still enjoy a range of shows while we’re all still in lockdown.&#xA;Shakespeare’s Globe Image: Shakespeare’s Globe&#xA;Between the years of 1592-93, The Globe was closed due to an outbreak of the plague. Although The Globe is currently closed again, fortunately this time around, you can still watch a selection of Shakespeare’s plays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitality In The Woods festival 2023 review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-festival-2023-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-festival-2023-review/</guid>
      <description>Hospitality in the Woods festival makes a triumphant return to London.&#xA;Image: Hospitality In The Woods 2023. Beckhenham Palace Park. © Trade Photographer.&#xA;Leaving the tram at Beckenham Junction, you’d have been hard pressed to believe there was anything significant going on in the town on Saturday as dog walkers and brunchers milled about, basking in the glorious summer weather. However, just a short walk away, Beckenham Place Park welcomed a sea of bucket hats and became home to one of the most recognisable festival in Drum &amp;amp; Bass for the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printworks London closure: the venue whose spirit lives on</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/printworks-closure-the-venue-whose-spirit-lives-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/printworks-closure-the-venue-whose-spirit-lives-on/</guid>
      <description>The closure of Printworks marks the end of an era for London&amp;rsquo;s clubbing scene, but the legacy of this iconic venue will undoubtedly live on.&#xA;Image: Closing weekend at Printworks London. © Emma Chadwick&#xA;It was a sad weekend for London’s ravers as the iconic Printworks nightclub closed its doors for the last time. Artists including Peggy Gou, Sub Focus and Black Coffee gathered in the press halls for a final send-off, creating the fantastic atmosphere and energy that the venue is known and loved for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why have female leaders been so successful in handling the coronavirus pandemic?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfrsk515mq9798w8cyuh8g8fmvwwi1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfrsk515mq9798w8cyuh8g8fmvwwi1/</guid>
      <description>In the last few weeks, the UK has watched as its European neighbours have started to reopen shops, meet with family members and enjoy some semblance of life before lockdown. Like a naughty child, confined to its room, watching his friends from the window as they play outside, the UK public have become increasingly frustrated.&#xA;Although the outbreak of coronavirus is a global pandemic, nations around the world have responded differently with countries such as Germany and New Zealand having relatively more success compared to the UK, America and Brazil who have experienced the highest death tolls.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
