<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London15 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/london15/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London15 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/london15/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in June in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>June in London is buzzing with excitement as festival season kicks off and some much-loved events return. From Southbank Centre&amp;rsquo;s Meltdown festival, curated by the legendary Chaka Khan, to the delightful lunchtime Jazz Series at Cadogan Hall. Add in the Sundance Film Festival and the revival of Open Water Swimming, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got a month packed with fantastic activities. Here&amp;rsquo;s our selection of things to do in London this June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to find public art in London right now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-public-art-in-london-this-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-public-art-in-london-this-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>Summer in London offers the perfect opportunity to delve into the city&amp;rsquo;s fantastic public art trails. With the resurgence of public art programmes at The Southbank Centre, alongside the public art trail associated with Chelsea and Kensington Art Week, as well as permanent fixtures like The Line in East London and the last opportunity to view sculptures from the 12th edition of Sculptures in the City, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty to explore. Here&amp;rsquo;s our guide on when and where to experience free public art in London this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterclass, Southbank Centre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/masterclass-southbank-centre-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/masterclass-southbank-centre-review/</guid>
      <description>The ‘Mr Nasty of American Theatre’ gets his comeuppance in this comedic dissection of the white male artist, which lifts the lid on issues that continue to plague the creative industries.&#xA;Irish theatre company Brokentalkers and artist Adrienne Truscott. make their London debut at the Southbank Centre with Masterclass. Photo by Ste Murray.&#xA;Following a hit international tour, Irish theatre company Brokentalkers and artist Adrienne Truscott make their London debut at the Southbank Centre with Masterclass, a witty examination of gender and power in the arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art exhibitions to watch out for in London in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-to-watch-out-for-in-london-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-to-watch-out-for-in-london-in-2025/</guid>
      <description>Announcements are already rolling in for London’s 2025 art exhibitions, and the line-up is shaping up splendidly. Highlights include the UK’s first exhibition dedicated to José María Velasco, Mexico’s acclaimed 19th-century painter, and the Royal Academy’s Brasil! Brasil! The Birth of Modernism, featuring over 130 works by ten prominent Brazilian artists. The newly opened V&amp;amp;A East Museum will debut The Music Is Black: A British Story, while next year will also bring two major Van Gogh exhibitions—one at the National Gallery and another at the Royal Academy of Arts, where Anselm Kiefer’s work will be shown in dialogue with Van Gogh’s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to find London&#39;s best ice cream parlours this summer 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>London’s summer weather may be unpredictable, but its ice cream parlours are always ready for sunny days. From the return of Anya Hindmarch’s Ice Cream Project to delicious soft serve in Chinatown and neighbourhood favourite Udderlicious, here are some of our top spots to enjoy ice cream in London this summer.&#xA;The Ice Cream Project III Anya Hindmarch ice cream project III. Photo by MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Returning for its third year, The Ice Cream Project is back at The Village from 7 June to 18 August, offering unexpectedly delicious ice creams and sorbets inspired by Anya Hindmarch&amp;rsquo;s favourite cult food brands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
