<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Much Ado About Nothing, Shakespeare&#39;s Globe Theatre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/much-ado-about-nothing-shakespeares-globe-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/much-ado-about-nothing-shakespeares-globe-review/</guid>
      <description>The Globe’s 2024 summer season is off to a flying start with a joyous romp through one of Shakespeare’s much-loved comedies.&#xA;Ekow Quartey as Benedick and Amalia Vitale as Beatrice. Photography by Marc Brenner.&#xA;Sean Holmes’ production of Much Ado About Nothing is the kind of Shakespeare GCSE English teachers dream about. We are transported to the warm and hazy summer days of sixteenth century Italy, where trees are laden with ripening oranges, noblemen stroll through sun-dappled orchards and evenings are filled with the lively intricacies of dances and music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterclass, Southbank Centre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/masterclass-southbank-centre-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/masterclass-southbank-centre-review/</guid>
      <description>The ‘Mr Nasty of American Theatre’ gets his comeuppance in this comedic dissection of the white male artist, which lifts the lid on issues that continue to plague the creative industries.&#xA;Irish theatre company Brokentalkers and artist Adrienne Truscott. make their London debut at the Southbank Centre with Masterclass. Photo by Ste Murray.&#xA;Following a hit international tour, Irish theatre company Brokentalkers and artist Adrienne Truscott make their London debut at the Southbank Centre with Masterclass, a witty examination of gender and power in the arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahmed Mater: Chronicles at Christie&#39;s London review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ahmed-mater-chronicles-at-christies-london-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ahmed-mater-chronicles-at-christies-london-review/</guid>
      <description>Christie’s has a wonderful summer treat for us all with their exhibition for the summer featuring Ahmed Mater, a leading Saudi Contemporary Artist. This exhibition, to date, is the most comprehensive dedicated to Ahmed Mater. I have become acutely aware my knowledge of artists from Asia and the Middle East is greatly lacking and I found this free exhibition to be a wonderful introduction which I am sure will propel me to seek out more work of artists from these regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIANA The Untold and Untrue Story at the King&#39;s Head Theatre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-the-untold-and-untrue-story-at-the-kings-head-theatre-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-the-untold-and-untrue-story-at-the-kings-head-theatre-review/</guid>
      <description>After a sold-out Edinburgh Fringe run in 2023 and winning the OffFest Award for Best Play, Diana - The Untold and Untrue Story has arrived in London for a three-week run at the King’s Head Theatre in Islington. Let me start by saying it is the best and silliest kind of fun and the most I’ve laughed in such a short space of time. Book it!&#xA;Diana the Untrue and Untold Story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: 13th Edition of Sculpture in the City 2024, City of London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/13th-edition-of-sculpture-in-the-city-2024-city-of-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/13th-edition-of-sculpture-in-the-city-2024-city-of-london/</guid>
      <description>We were keen to receive an invitation to tour this year’s 13th Edition of Sculpture in the City. There is something about public sculpture, which is extremely appealing, with each sculpture displayed with its own unique back drop and surroundings and the opportunity of accidental interaction with the art.&#xA;Temple, Richard Mackness, part of the 13th edition of Sculpture in the City. © Richard Mackness. Photo © Nick Turpin.&#xA;Having lived in Sydney for 13 years Sculpture by the Sea (begins mid-October) was one of my favourite events of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL, Mohamed Jabaly, SAFAR Film Festival</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-life-is-beautiful-mohamed-jabaly-safar-film-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-life-is-beautiful-mohamed-jabaly-safar-film-festival/</guid>
      <description>The opening documentary of this year’s SAFAR Film Festival is a moving, first-person account of Mohamed Jabaly’s experience of travelling abroad and finding himself stranded, unable to return to his home in Gaza, forced to watch war unfold through his phone screen, and the community that forms around him as he fights to remain in a country that considers him stateless.&#xA;Life Is Beautiful.&#xA;Palestine is at the heart of this year’s SAFAR Film Festival, the largest festival in the UK dedicated to cinema from the Arab world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: We wear our wheels with pride by Robyn Orlin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</guid>
      <description>I have arrived at the last of the four Van Cleef &amp;amp; Arpel Dance Reflection evenings I chose to review, and I am now wishing I had the energy and time see every show of this contemporary dance festival. It has been a wonderfully diverse showcase, and it seems I saved the most joyous for last.&#xA;The full title of this piece—WE WEAR OUR WHEELS WITH PRIDE AND SLAP YOUR STREET WITH COLOR&amp;hellip; WE SAID “BONJOUR” TO SATAN IN 1820—is a homage to the rickshaw drivers of Durban by South African choreographer, Robyn Orlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Academy Summer Exhibition 2025 review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</guid>
      <description>Arriving right on cue with the first wafts of summer London heat, the Royal Academy Summer Show has returned for its 257th exhibition. Curated under the theme of ‘Dialogues,’ the 2025 edition is coordinated by internationally acclaimed architect and Royal Academician Farshid Moussavi and explores art’s capacity to forge dialogues and build sensitivity towards societal concerns such as ecology, survival and living together. As Moussavi explained: “These dialogues can be between people of different races, genders, or cultures; between humans, all species, and the planet; or across different disciplines - art, science, politics for example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOZI Restaurant Victoria Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</guid>
      <description>TOZI, derived from the affectionate Venetian slang for “a close-knit group of friends,” is the brainchild of an Italian trio that met while opening Shoreditch House under the Soho House Group. In 2013, Chef Maurilio Molteni, fresh from his time as Head Chef at Shoreditch House and developing the menu at Cecconi’s, opened the first TOZI restaurant in London. He was joined by Stefano Meloni and Marco Bullegas as restaurant manager and bar manager, respectively.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
