<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London2 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London2 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: best walks in London</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flofavourites-best-walks-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flofavourites-best-walks-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Walks have been very in vogue over the last few months, and London really does have a whole host of amazing locations for a wander. From an art-filled strolls, to walks along the Thames, here are some of our favourite places to walk around in the city.&#xA;The Line Image: Alex Chinneck&#xA;The Line is a 7.7km route from Queen Elizabeth Olympic Park to the O2 that follows the line of Greenwich Meridian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: top 5 in food this week</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</guid>
      <description>We are into the fourth week of the government’s new ‘Eat Out to Help Out!’ scheme. It came into effect on 3 August and lasts till the end of the month, giving people 50% off their bill at thousands of restaurants across the country on Mondays, Tuesdays and Wednesdays. The scheme is designed to encourage us all to get out there and support the hospitality industry following the nationwide lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be in the Know: Crossrail</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/be-in-the-know-crossrail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/be-in-the-know-crossrail/</guid>
      <description>Crossrail is an infrastructure project that is under construction to deliver a new railway through Central London. The new railway will be known as the Elizabeth Line and will be run by Transport for London (TfL). The line, once complete, will run from Reading and Heathrow in the west, to Shenfield and Abbey Wood in the east.&#xA;Image: Crossrail route maps&#xA;The route will serve 41 stations, 10 of which are new.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhibitions not to miss in London this August 2020</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-this-month-in-art-q4wqv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-this-month-in-art-q4wqv/</guid>
      <description>Toyin Ojih Odutola: A Countervailing Theory When: The Barbican&#xA;When: 11 August – 23 August 2020&#xA;**Price:**Free&#xA;Image: Babrican&#xA;**#FLODown:**The Barbican’s art gallery, The Curve, presents the works of Nigerian-American artist Toyin Ojih Odutola. Odutola explores an imagined ancient myth, with an immersive accompanying soundscape by artist Peter Adjaye. Odutola plays with the notion that drawing can be a form of storytelling, and challenges viewers to piece together fragments of the stories she presents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhibitions not to miss in London this September 2020</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/htwjtzletaqacofx88prfpyh4zapsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/htwjtzletaqacofx88prfpyh4zapsr/</guid>
      <description>London Grads Now Where?&#xA;Saatchi Gallery&#xA;When?&#xA;3 September – 25 September 2020&#xA;Price: £3&#xA;Image: MTotoe&#xA;#FLODown: Saatchi Gallery reopens on Thursday 3 September with London Grads Now. The exhibition will bring together the works of over 150 graduating artists from London’s leading fine arts schools includingRoyal College of Art, UCL: Slade School of Art, Goldsmiths: University of London, UAL: Chelsea College of Arts, UAL: Wimbledon College of Arts, UAL: Camberwell College of ArtsandUAL: Central Saint Martins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The London Diaries: the copywriter living at home</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/london-diaries-25-30k-in-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/london-diaries-25-30k-in-the-city/</guid>
      <description>Job: Copywriter&#xA;Time living in London: Prior to the COVID-19 pandemic, I lived in London Bridge and then Waterloo for a year. Now I live at home with my mum.&#xA;Area: Sutton&#xA;Pay range: £25,000 - £30,000&#xA;Relationship status: Single&#xA;Rent: £100 – a token gesture.&#xA;Monday Due to the pandemic, I’ve been working from home since March which has been a great opportunity to get extensive wear out of my pyjamas and gym gear.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
