<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Corona on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/corona/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Corona on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/corona/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Dr Zara Benjamin-Laing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-dr-zara-benjamin-laing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-dr-zara-benjamin-laing/</guid>
      <description>We had a chat with Dr Zara to discover what a day in the life at Birmingham hospital amid the coronavirus pandemic.&#xA;Key workers have been working tirelessly on the front line throughout our nation’s battle against coronavirus. We caught up with NHS doctor, Zara Benjamin-Laing, to discover how day-to-day life has changed at the hospital she works at amid the current pandemic.&#xA;Image: Zara Benjamin-Laing&#xA;Dr Zara Benjamin-Laing is a Senior House Officer (SHO) currently working in Birmingham.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working from home: love it or hate it, it’s here to stay, so let’s make it work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/working-from-home-love-it-or-hate-it-its-here-to-stay-so-lets-make-it-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/working-from-home-love-it-or-hate-it-its-here-to-stay-so-lets-make-it-work/</guid>
      <description>I had never been one for working from home before the lockdown, claiming that my job wasn’t really do-able from home (I can now safely say that’s not the case). But now that I’ve been forced to, I’m quite enjoying working from home and I hope that in some capacity it will stick. Here are some of the things that I’ve found useful for making it work (excuse the pun).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual dating during lockdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/love-lockdown-virtual-dating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/love-lockdown-virtual-dating/</guid>
      <description>With the devastating news that Love Island 2020 has been cancelled due to COVID-19, FLO London is here to help fill that void and give you some tips for a thriving virtual dating life. Who would have thought that hit Netflix shows Love is Blind and Too Hot to Handle would somehow become a reality for single people around the world? Is it possible to form a ‘deep connection’ with someone you’ve never met before?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to protect yourself from coronavirus (COVID-19) on public transport</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-protect-yourself-from-coronavirus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-protect-yourself-from-coronavirus/</guid>
      <description>What is the Coronavirus? By now we are all familiar with the term &amp;lsquo;coronavirus&amp;rsquo;. The virus currently infecting people around the world is COVID-19. COVID-19 is a member of the coronavirus family, which has never been detected until now.&#xA;Coronaviruses (CoV) are a large family of viruses that cause illnesses ranging from the common cold to serious diseases such as severe acute respiratory syndrome. Coronaviruses are zoonotic, meaning they are transmitted between animals and people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why have female leaders been so successful in handling the coronavirus pandemic?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfrsk515mq9798w8cyuh8g8fmvwwi1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfrsk515mq9798w8cyuh8g8fmvwwi1/</guid>
      <description>In the last few weeks, the UK has watched as its European neighbours have started to reopen shops, meet with family members and enjoy some semblance of life before lockdown. Like a naughty child, confined to its room, watching his friends from the window as they play outside, the UK public have become increasingly frustrated.&#xA;Although the outbreak of coronavirus is a global pandemic, nations around the world have responded differently with countries such as Germany and New Zealand having relatively more success compared to the UK, America and Brazil who have experienced the highest death tolls.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
