<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Feat2 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/feat2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Feat2 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/feat2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in June in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>June in London is buzzing with excitement as festival season kicks off and some much-loved events return. From Southbank Centre&amp;rsquo;s Meltdown festival, curated by the legendary Chaka Khan, to the delightful lunchtime Jazz Series at Cadogan Hall. Add in the Sundance Film Festival and the revival of Open Water Swimming, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got a month packed with fantastic activities. Here&amp;rsquo;s our selection of things to do in London this June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to find public art in London right now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-public-art-in-london-this-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-public-art-in-london-this-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>Summer in London offers the perfect opportunity to delve into the city&amp;rsquo;s fantastic public art trails. With the resurgence of public art programmes at The Southbank Centre, alongside the public art trail associated with Chelsea and Kensington Art Week, as well as permanent fixtures like The Line in East London and the last opportunity to view sculptures from the 12th edition of Sculptures in the City, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty to explore. Here&amp;rsquo;s our guide on when and where to experience free public art in London this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterclass, Southbank Centre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/masterclass-southbank-centre-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/masterclass-southbank-centre-review/</guid>
      <description>The ‘Mr Nasty of American Theatre’ gets his comeuppance in this comedic dissection of the white male artist, which lifts the lid on issues that continue to plague the creative industries.&#xA;Irish theatre company Brokentalkers and artist Adrienne Truscott. make their London debut at the Southbank Centre with Masterclass. Photo by Ste Murray.&#xA;Following a hit international tour, Irish theatre company Brokentalkers and artist Adrienne Truscott make their London debut at the Southbank Centre with Masterclass, a witty examination of gender and power in the arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A guide to events not to miss at London Craft Week 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/events-not-to-miss-at-london-craft-week-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/events-not-to-miss-at-london-craft-week-2024/</guid>
      <description>London Craft Week 2024 returns this week for its 10th edition, running from 13 - 19 May 2024, highlighting British and international creativity by showcasing over 750 established and emerging makers, designers, brands, and galleries. The festival offers a curated selection of events that promise to inspire and help you discover some of the great talent right on our doorstep! Here are eight notable events to explore during London Craft Week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hart Shoreditch Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hart-shoreditch-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hart-shoreditch-review/</guid>
      <description>Hart Shoreditch, situated in the vibrant heart of Shoreditch, provides a charming and sophisticated retreat that captures the essence of the local area.&#xA;Image: Hart Shoreditch&#xA;Located in the beating heart of Shoerditch, Hart Shoreditch offers a cosy, laid back and elegant base in which to explore all the local area has to offer. Inspired by East London’s past, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique design is a celebration of Shoreditch and its heritage as a centre for craftspeople and makers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Cordon Bleu to hold Summer Festival in London in July</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/le-cordon-bleu-to-hold-summer-festival-in-london-in-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/le-cordon-bleu-to-hold-summer-festival-in-london-in-july/</guid>
      <description>Le Cordon Bleu London&amp;rsquo;s Summer Festival 2023 is coming to London in July 2023 and will feature cooking demonstrations, workshops, wine tastings, and guest chef showcases by renowned culinary talents.&#xA;Image: Le Cordon Bleu London&#xA;Le Cordon Bleu London is gearing up for their highly anticipated annual Summer Festival, set to be held at their institute in Bloomsbury. Taking place on 1 July 2023, the festival promises a delightful array of activities to entice culinary enthusiasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Soojin Kang</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-soojin-kang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-soojin-kang/</guid>
      <description>“My work speaks with emotion. The surfaces I weave, the positive and negative space that becomes the forms that I create…”&#xA;- Soojin Kang&#xA;Image: Soojin Kang. © Markus Schroder&#xA;Soojin Kang is a Korean artist now based in Germany, whose practice is based on the exploration of textiles as a sculptural medium. Using the ritualistic actions of weaving, knotting, winding and unwinding, she transubstantiates raw materials into structures that retain unmistakeable traces of their biotic origins through rough surfaces and natural dyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Dr Zara Benjamin-Laing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-dr-zara-benjamin-laing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-dr-zara-benjamin-laing/</guid>
      <description>We had a chat with Dr Zara to discover what a day in the life at Birmingham hospital amid the coronavirus pandemic.&#xA;Key workers have been working tirelessly on the front line throughout our nation’s battle against coronavirus. We caught up with NHS doctor, Zara Benjamin-Laing, to discover how day-to-day life has changed at the hospital she works at amid the current pandemic.&#xA;Image: Zara Benjamin-Laing&#xA;Dr Zara Benjamin-Laing is a Senior House Officer (SHO) currently working in Birmingham.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working from home: love it or hate it, it’s here to stay, so let’s make it work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/working-from-home-love-it-or-hate-it-its-here-to-stay-so-lets-make-it-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/working-from-home-love-it-or-hate-it-its-here-to-stay-so-lets-make-it-work/</guid>
      <description>I had never been one for working from home before the lockdown, claiming that my job wasn’t really do-able from home (I can now safely say that’s not the case). But now that I’ve been forced to, I’m quite enjoying working from home and I hope that in some capacity it will stick. Here are some of the things that I’ve found useful for making it work (excuse the pun).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual dating during lockdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/love-lockdown-virtual-dating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/love-lockdown-virtual-dating/</guid>
      <description>With the devastating news that Love Island 2020 has been cancelled due to COVID-19, FLO London is here to help fill that void and give you some tips for a thriving virtual dating life. Who would have thought that hit Netflix shows Love is Blind and Too Hot to Handle would somehow become a reality for single people around the world? Is it possible to form a ‘deep connection’ with someone you’ve never met before?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLODown: Pizzeria Mozza</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flodown-pizzeria-mozza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flodown-pizzeria-mozza/</guid>
      <description>Image: @pizza_diaries_ldn&#xA;It’s been a while since I’ve been on the pizza trail, or rather the pizza-in-actual-establishments trail. I was delighted when @marinagpoloughlin writing a sterling review of a new LA pizzeria in Oxford Circus coincided with my company opening an office nearby. Having excitedly told anyone I’d encountered at the office opening about my desire to try this (whilst letting them know I have a pizza blog), I managed to drag a few colleagues out of the local pubs and into the pizzeria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: top 5 in food this week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</guid>
      <description>We are into the fourth week of the government’s new ‘Eat Out to Help Out!’ scheme. It came into effect on 3 August and lasts till the end of the month, giving people 50% off their bill at thousands of restaurants across the country on Mondays, Tuesdays and Wednesdays. The scheme is designed to encourage us all to get out there and support the hospitality industry following the nationwide lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 unmissable art fairs and events in London for 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/22-unmissable-art-fairs-and-events-in-london-for-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/22-unmissable-art-fairs-and-events-in-london-for-2025/</guid>
      <description>This year, London will host an array of art fairs, art weeks, and design festivals, showcasing everything from photography and contemporary art to ceramics, antiques, sculpture, and innovative design. The 2025 art scene will be as vibrant as ever, featuring long-established events like Frieze, LAPADA, and the London Design Festival, as well as exciting newcomers such as Fresh: Art Fair and the return of the London Design Biennale. With various art weeks, including Clerkenwell Design Week, also on the calendar, here’s a guide to twenty-two unmissable art fairs, events, and festivals in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 great ideas for enjoying a last-minute holiday in Prague</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/4-great-ideas-for-enjoying-a-last-minute-holiday-in-prague/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/4-great-ideas-for-enjoying-a-last-minute-holiday-in-prague/</guid>
      <description>Discover the charms of spontaneous travel in Prague, where you can enjoy adventures amid its rich culture and scenic beauty.&#xA;Image: Charles Bridge in Prague during sunset. © Jay Ngai&#xA;Tourism in Prague is thriving, which means it&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to visit. The city collaborates with the PCT each year to promote domestic tourism and welcome tourists. According to František Cipro, director of Prague City Tourism (PCT), Prague will welcome nearly eight million visitors in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antisemitism 101</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/antisemitism-101-rsfue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/antisemitism-101-rsfue/</guid>
      <description>Antisemitism is horrible. As with any discrimination, it taps into the worst corner of the human psyche – the dark feeling of control which flickers within a person when they abuse another simply because they are different or unfamiliar. Whilst Wiley was enjoying such crude empowerment when he spent over 12 hours last week bombarding social media with his antisemitic posts, Jewish people all over the world including myself were left bruised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art exhibitions to watch out for in London in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-to-watch-out-for-in-london-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-to-watch-out-for-in-london-in-2025/</guid>
      <description>Announcements are already rolling in for London’s 2025 art exhibitions, and the line-up is shaping up splendidly. Highlights include the UK’s first exhibition dedicated to José María Velasco, Mexico’s acclaimed 19th-century painter, and the Royal Academy’s Brasil! Brasil! The Birth of Modernism, featuring over 130 works by ten prominent Brazilian artists. The newly opened V&amp;amp;A East Museum will debut The Music Is Black: A British Story, while next year will also bring two major Van Gogh exhibitions—one at the National Gallery and another at the Royal Academy of Arts, where Anselm Kiefer’s work will be shown in dialogue with Van Gogh’s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be in the Know: Crossrail</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/be-in-the-know-crossrail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/be-in-the-know-crossrail/</guid>
      <description>Crossrail is an infrastructure project that is under construction to deliver a new railway through Central London. The new railway will be known as the Elizabeth Line and will be run by Transport for London (TfL). The line, once complete, will run from Reading and Heathrow in the west, to Shenfield and Abbey Wood in the east.&#xA;Image: Crossrail route maps&#xA;The route will serve 41 stations, 10 of which are new.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best restaurants to eat light and wholesome food in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Discover London&amp;rsquo;s top destinations for light, nutritious, and wholesome food with our guide. From the ever-popular vegetarian favourite KIN Cafe to the renowned Maggie Jones&amp;rsquo;s, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a range of options to satisfy your cravings.&#xA;Image: Dan Gold&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a dining experience in London that is both delicious and nutritious, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. Our six restaurant recommendations offer a delightful selection of light, flavourful meals that are not only wholesome but also leave you feeling energised and fully satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Lives Matter: anti-racist organisations to support in the UK</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/black-lives-matter-how-you-can-help-w6pvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/black-lives-matter-how-you-can-help-w6pvt/</guid>
      <description>The recent death of George Floyd, Breonna Taylor and Ahmaud Arbery in America has sparked global outrage. Thousands of anti-racism protesters across the world are demanding justice for these individuals, and are highlighting the widespread racial injustices that occur daily. Racial issues are not just unique to the US, this is a global issue that we must all work together to solve.&#xA;Over the coming weeks we will sharing a huge range of resources to help you on your journey to education on this topic, and we have been sharing lots of information on our social media too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canary Wharf’s Winter Lights Festival to return in January 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/canary-wharfs-winter-lights-festival-to-return-january-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/canary-wharfs-winter-lights-festival-to-return-january-2025/</guid>
      <description>London’s dazzling Winter Lights festival returns with 11 new installations and iconic displays, transforming Canary Wharf from 21 January 2025.&#xA;The Clew by Ottotto&#xA;Canary Wharf’s Winter Lights festival returns this January for its ninth edition, bringing with it a blend of light-based art installations from both renowned and emerging artists worldwide. The free, annual event has become a much-anticipated fixture for Londoners and visitors alike, as the neighbourhood is transformed into a vibrant, luminous wonderland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover exceptional jazz at Ladbroke Hall this April</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-month-of-exceptional-jazz-at-ladbroke-hall-this-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-month-of-exceptional-jazz-at-ladbroke-hall-this-april/</guid>
      <description>This April, Ladbroke Hall’s renowned Friday Jazz &amp;amp; Dinner series returns, showcasing an impressive roster of artists at its Sunbeam Theatre. Each evening pairs exceptional live jazz with a carefully crafted menu from the award-winning Pollini restaurant. With tickets priced at £15 for standing and £30 for table seating, the series offers an intimate setting to enjoy world-class music in the heart of West London.&#xA;© Ladbroke Hall&#xA;The month opens on 4 April with saxophonist Alex Garnett, who will be joined by Will Barry (piano), Ferg Ireland (double bass), and Will Cleasby (drums).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLO London x British Vogue 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flo-london-x-british-vogue-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flo-london-x-british-vogue-2022/</guid>
      <description>FLO London features in the June, July and August 2022 issues of British Vogue. As a female-owned business this has been a wonderful opportunity and a chance to showcase our newest collection of Ghanaian wax print products made from Nsubra fabrics.&#xA;“I created FLO London The Shop with the intent of relaying the meanings and beauty of some of the wonderful Ghanaian wax print fabrics I have been in awe of my whole life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel Athens Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/four-seasons-astir-palace-hotel-athens-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/four-seasons-astir-palace-hotel-athens-review/</guid>
      <description>Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel Athens is a remarkable hotel that offers a luxurious experience and a tranquil and rejuvenating vacation.&#xA;Image: Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel, Athens, March 2023, © MTotoe&#xA;The Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel is a luxurious seaside escape located on a pine-clad peninsula in the Athenian Riviera, just 30 minutes away from the historical city centre of Athens and the Athens International Airport. With a rich history dating back to 1958, the hotel underwent a €650 million renovation in 2019 and boasts a unique blend of modern luxury and heritage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiroshi Sugimoto: Time Machine at The Hayward Gallery review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hiroshi-sugimoto-time-machine-at-the-hayward-gallery-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hiroshi-sugimoto-time-machine-at-the-hayward-gallery-review/</guid>
      <description>Hiroshi Sugimoto’s awe-inspiring photographs are currently on display at the Hayward Gallery. It is the largest survey to date of this artist in the UK and it is spellbinding, some rooms much more than others. For over 50 years, Sugimoto has been creating multiple extraordinary, enigmatic photographic series playing with light and dark, life and death, and these are all now on display for us to admire and question what is truth and what is not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitality in the Woods returns to London in August 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-returns-to-london-nbspin-august-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-returns-to-london-nbspin-august-2023/</guid>
      <description>Hospitality in the Woods makes its comeback to the picturesque Beckenham Place Park in August 2023, featuring a jam-packed lineup of Drum &amp;amp; Bass stars.&#xA;Image: Hospitality In The Woods.&#xA;Get ready for the return of Hospitality In The Woods, a legendary showcase of Drum &amp;amp; Bass excellence set to take place on 19 August at Beckenham Place Park. Headlined by Netsky and High Contrast, this electrifying festival will feature five curated stages of non-stop, banging music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Elisabeth Mulenga</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-elisabeth-mulenga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-elisabeth-mulenga/</guid>
      <description>“As a performer, a lot of my inspiration comes from a desire to experience different versions of myself, access different identities…”&#xA;- Elisabeth Mulenga&#xA;Image: Elisabeth Mulenga. © Jack Thomson.&#xA;Elisabeth Mulenga is a dance artist whose work is at once unflinching, tender, and intimate, and takes inspiration from film directors to explore the human psyche. Mulenga is an alumnus of the eighth cohort of National Youth Dance Company (NYDC) and won the Choreographic Innovation Award in the final of BBC Young Dancer 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Joanna van Son</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-joanna-van-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-joanna-van-son/</guid>
      <description>“Painting turns images into objects, and objects into fields of disoriented depths deeper than the flat edge of the canvas.”&#xA;- Joanna van Son&#xA;Image: Joanna van Son&#xA;Joanna van Son is a fine artist based in London. Born in Oman to Venezuelan/Irish and Dutch parents, she grew up in China, Russia, and the United Kingdom, and from a young age was attracted to the intensity of bodily representations in Baroque art, taking particular interest in the dynamic figurations in the paintings of Old Master Caravaggio, as well as Cecily Brown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Nicole Schoeni</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nicole-schoeni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nicole-schoeni/</guid>
      <description>“What I really love to do is to support artists and to be a patron and to share stories.”&#xA;- Nicole Schoeni&#xA;Image: Nicole Schoeni. Schoeni Projects&#xA;Nicole is an experienced gallerist and gallery director, and the founder of Schoeni Projects. She has lived in Hong Kong for most of her life, although attended school and university in the UK. Contemporary and street art are two of her passions, although what she really loves the most about the art world is collaborating with creatives and meeting new people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Péjú Oshin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-pj-oshin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-pj-oshin/</guid>
      <description>“I also felt that my practice was liminal, because it&amp;rsquo;s between this space of architecture, writing, but also curating or education, a multitude of things.”&#xA;- Péjú Oshin&#xA;Image: Péjú Oshin. Photography by Jake Green, courtesy of Gagosian&#xA;Péjú Oshin’s career as a gallery curator was unexpected. After graduating with a degree in architecture, she found herself in the art world through volunteering and working with young people. Péjú&amp;rsquo;s commitment to community work and education led her to become a curator of Young People’s Programmes at Tate, landing her on Forbes 30 Under 30 shortlist for Arts &amp;amp; Culture in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major exhibition of new and recent work by Peter Doig opens at The Courtauld</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/major-exhibition-of-new-and-recent-work-by-peter-doig-opens-at-the-courtauld/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/major-exhibition-of-new-and-recent-work-by-peter-doig-opens-at-the-courtauld/</guid>
      <description>The Morgan Stanley Exhibition: Peter Doig presents a new chapter in the career of one of the world’s leading artists. Featuring new and recent paintings, including a new London subject.&#xA;Image: The Morgan Stanley Exhibition Peter Doig at The Courtauld, 2023. © Photo Fergus Carmichael.&#xA;A major exhibition of new and recent works by Peter Doig opens at The Courtauld on 10 February 2023. Featuring 12 paintings and 19 works on paper, the exhibition will include a group of major canvases created since the artist’s move from Trinidad to London in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Margaret Ngigi Exhibition at Doyle Wham</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/margaret-ngigi-exhibition-at-doyle-wham/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/margaret-ngigi-exhibition-at-doyle-wham/</guid>
      <description>Location: Doyle Wham, 43 Ebury Bridge Road, SW1W 8PX&#xA;Date: Until 31st January 2020&#xA;Price: Free&#xA;Image: Murky Waters I, Margaret Ngigi via Doyle Wham&#xA;Doyle Wham presents the first solo exhibition of Kenyan based photographer and filmmaker, Margaret Ngigi, in the UK. The exhibition explores the complex pressures facing young women in contemporary Kenyan society. Ngigi states that “Murky Waters is my way of examining the challenges that women still face in society, by illustrating the positions we are forced into, and the situations that different groups of women find themselves in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford Street Christmas lights to return in November</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</guid>
      <description>Oxford Street&amp;rsquo;s dazzling Christmas lights are poised to make a grand return on 2 November, ushering in the festive spirit throughout London.&#xA;Image: Oxford Street Christmas lights to return 2 November 2023.&#xA;On 2 November, the festive season will kick off on Oxford Street as its renowned Christmas lights illuminate the iconic London street. The city&amp;rsquo;s ultimate holiday destination will shine brightly with brilliant white stars (and lots of people capturing Instagram-worthy pictures), creating that magical Christmas atmosphere we associate with London during this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photography exhibitions to see in London now and in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/photography-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-now-and-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/photography-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-now-and-in-2025/</guid>
      <description>London is currently hosting an array of photography exhibitions offering compelling reflections on nature, identity, and urban life — with even more set to open in the later stages of 2025. From Wildlife Photographer of the Year at the Natural History Museum, which highlights the beauty and fragility of the natural world, to Gabriel Moses’ exhibition at 180 Studios, showcasing his work across fashion, music, and sport. The Photographers’ Gallery offers a glimpse into the changing landscape of Leeds with a Peter Mitchell retrospective, while Nature Study at the V&amp;amp;A explores ecological themes through the contemporary photobook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick &amp; easy recipes: The veggie salad edition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/quickamp-easy-recipes-the-veggie-salad-edition-oftjg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/quickamp-easy-recipes-the-veggie-salad-edition-oftjg/</guid>
      <description>Here is a guide to some of our favourite nutritious vegetarian salad recipes that are quick and easy to make! Whether you’re big on sweet potato salads, love a salad bursting with your favourite greens or perhaps your looking for something a bit more unique, such as a kiwi salad. We have a bit of everything for you…&#xA;The green feast ﻿ Broccoli, Courgette and Avocado Salad This is sure to become one of your favourite salads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: 13th Edition of Sculpture in the City 2024, City of London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/13th-edition-of-sculpture-in-the-city-2024-city-of-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/13th-edition-of-sculpture-in-the-city-2024-city-of-london/</guid>
      <description>We were keen to receive an invitation to tour this year’s 13th Edition of Sculpture in the City. There is something about public sculpture, which is extremely appealing, with each sculpture displayed with its own unique back drop and surroundings and the opportunity of accidental interaction with the art.&#xA;Temple, Richard Mackness, part of the 13th edition of Sculpture in the City. © Richard Mackness. Photo © Nick Turpin.&#xA;Having lived in Sydney for 13 years Sculpture by the Sea (begins mid-October) was one of my favourite events of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: We wear our wheels with pride by Robyn Orlin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</guid>
      <description>I have arrived at the last of the four Van Cleef &amp;amp; Arpel Dance Reflection evenings I chose to review, and I am now wishing I had the energy and time see every show of this contemporary dance festival. It has been a wonderfully diverse showcase, and it seems I saved the most joyous for last.&#xA;The full title of this piece—WE WEAR OUR WHEELS WITH PRIDE AND SLAP YOUR STREET WITH COLOR&amp;hellip; WE SAID “BONJOUR” TO SATAN IN 1820—is a homage to the rickshaw drivers of Durban by South African choreographer, Robyn Orlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOLAIRE CULTURE, An Exhibition Celebrating 250 Years of Veuve Clicquot will open in London in May 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/solaire-culture-an-exhibition-celebrating-250-years-of-veuve-clicquot-will-open-in-london-in-may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/solaire-culture-an-exhibition-celebrating-250-years-of-veuve-clicquot-will-open-in-london-in-may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Veuve Clicquot announces today the next chapter of the highly successful global exhibition, SOLAIRE CULTURE, to celebrate 250 years of the iconic house. After debuting in Tokyo and Los Angeles in 2022, the exhibition is travelling to London, to take over Piccadilly Circus in May 2023.&#xA;Image: Veuve Clicquot “Solaire Culture” exhibition, Yayoi Kusama, Tokyo, 2022&#xA;SOLAIRE CULTURE celebrates Veuve Clicquot&amp;rsquo;s 250 years of history, focusing on the legacy of Madame Clicquot, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s first female entrepreneurs who took over the reins of the house in 1805, and the contemporary vision of the curator, Camille Morineau, and designer Constance Guisset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southbank Centre’s new Festival “Multitudes” to open in April 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/southbank-centres-new-festival-multitudes-to-open-in-april-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/southbank-centres-new-festival-multitudes-to-open-in-april-2025/</guid>
      <description>Multitudes at Southbank Centre will reimagine live music through bold collaborations across dance, theatre, and visual arts.&#xA;LPO x Circa: Daphnis and Chloe. © Laura Manariti.&#xA;Multitudes is an exciting new arts festival taking place at the Southbank Centre from 23 April to 3 May 2025. This festival reimagines the concert hall experience by blending orchestral music with a wide range of artistic disciplines, including dance, performance, spoken word, and visual arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The London Diaries: the copywriter living at home</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/london-diaries-25-30k-in-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/london-diaries-25-30k-in-the-city/</guid>
      <description>Job: Copywriter&#xA;Time living in London: Prior to the COVID-19 pandemic, I lived in London Bridge and then Waterloo for a year. Now I live at home with my mum.&#xA;Area: Sutton&#xA;Pay range: £25,000 - £30,000&#xA;Relationship status: Single&#xA;Rent: £100 – a token gesture.&#xA;Monday Due to the pandemic, I’ve been working from home since March which has been a great opportunity to get extensive wear out of my pyjamas and gym gear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Night Sky Concert Lab is coming to St John&#39;s Smith Square</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-night-sky-concert-lab-is-coming-to-st-johns-smith-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-night-sky-concert-lab-is-coming-to-st-johns-smith-square/</guid>
      <description>The Night Sky Concert Lab is going to be at St John’s Smith Square this November for two performances – one at 7pm and one at 9pm. The show will feature music from the Southbank Sinfonia, conducted by Olivia Clarke, and will be narrated by NASA astronaut Mike Massimino, whilst images from the James Webb Telescope are displayed.&#xA;This event promises to be an immersive, sonic journey into the cosmos that has been sparking curiosity since the beginning of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in November 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</guid>
      <description>November in London marks the return of many beloved Christmas traditions across the city. Highlights include the switching on of Christmas lights and the return of festive ice skating at Somerset House. Music enthusiasts can enjoy celebrations for 30 years of Bugged Out! at Drumsheds, along with performances of Hansel and Gretel at the Royal Opera House. The art scene will be vibrant with the opening of several new exhibitions, including an exploration of photography in Britain during the 80s at Tate Britain, as well as the return of the Woolwich Contemporary Print Fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in the Seychelles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-the-seychelles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-the-seychelles/</guid>
      <description>The Seychelles is an island nation made up of 115 islands (you can hop between islands via boat or plane, bear in mind a number of these islands are privately owned). With two UNESCO world heritage sites, the Seychelles also features the most breath-taking views you could ever imagine and is home to some of the most picturesque white sand beaches, delicious food and equally intriguing wildlife.&#xA;Here is our guide to some of the best things to do whilst on this tropical island…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOZI Restaurant Victoria Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</guid>
      <description>TOZI, derived from the affectionate Venetian slang for “a close-knit group of friends,” is the brainchild of an Italian trio that met while opening Shoreditch House under the Soho House Group. In 2013, Chef Maurilio Molteni, fresh from his time as Head Chef at Shoreditch House and developing the menu at Cecconi’s, opened the first TOZI restaurant in London. He was joined by Stefano Meloni and Marco Bullegas as restaurant manager and bar manager, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Jewish Film Festival</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/uk-jewish-film-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/uk-jewish-film-festival/</guid>
      <description>Founded in 1997, the UK Jewish Film Festival is an annual event which takes place for two weeks each November. This year, the festival has gone online, meaning that it provides an ideal opportunity to immerse yourself in Jewish film from the comfort of your own home. The festival began on 5 November and runs until 19 November, with a number of fantastic films and events yet to be broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V&amp;A to showcase first UK exhibition dedicated Fashion Designer Gabrielle ‘Coco’ Chanel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vampa-to-showcase-first-uk-exhibition-dedicated-fashion-designer-gabrielle-coco-chanel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vampa-to-showcase-first-uk-exhibition-dedicated-fashion-designer-gabrielle-coco-chanel/</guid>
      <description>The Victoria and Albert Museum (V&amp;amp;A) is set to host a landmark exhibition this September 2023, showcasing the pioneering work of fashion designer Gabrielle ‘Coco’ Chanel.&#xA;Image: Dorothy + Little Bara priest, Paris (Vogue) © 1960 William Klein&#xA;The V&amp;amp;A will be hosting the first-ever exhibition dedicated to the life and works of French couturière Gabrielle &amp;lsquo;Coco&amp;rsquo; Chanel. The exhibition will feature over 200 looks, along with accessories, perfumes, and jewelry that chart the evolution of Chanel&amp;rsquo;s iconic design style and the establishment of the House of CHANEL from 1910 to 1971.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegan food is not just for January, it’s for life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vegan-food-is-not-just-for-january-its-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vegan-food-is-not-just-for-january-its-for-life/</guid>
      <description>It was both extremely satisfying and hugely depressing to me that January ended on a Sunday this year. It looks lovely in the calendar but meant a long stretch till I could eat some cheese. I think it was actually really motivating to have something to focus on and pour my energy into considering the current lockdown, and I would actually recommend setting yourself a goal like this for the weeks moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 1 – 7 May 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-1-7-may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-1-7-may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 1 - 7 May 2023.&#xA;Explore London Unsound London&#xA;London&amp;rsquo;s groundbreaking Unsound event is returning after five years with three new works featuring innovative minds in electronic and experimental music. The boundary-pushing showcase includes performances by Osmium, a supergroup featuring Hildur Guðnadóttir, Sam Slater, James Ginzburg, and Rully Shabara of Senyawa. Custom-built instruments blend mechanical and organic sounds to create hypnotic music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 12 – 18 February 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-12-18-february-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-12-18-february-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 12 – 18 February 2024.&#xA;Guy Johnston and Britten Sinfonia: The Protecting Veil&#xA;Cellist Guy Johnston collaborates with Britten Sinfonia in a compelling concert featuring works by Tavener, Beethoven, and Bartók. Tavener&amp;rsquo;s The Protecting Veil showcases the cello&amp;rsquo;s emotive qualities, with Johnston&amp;rsquo;s performance reflecting his personal connection with the composer.&#xA;Date: 15 February 2024. Time: 7.30pm. Location: Barbican Centre, Silk Street, London</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 26 June – 2 July 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-26-june-2-july-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-26-june-2-july-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 26 June – 2 July 2023.&#xA;Explore London Chelsea &amp;amp; Kensington Festival 2023&#xA;Kensington and Chelsea Festival is returning for its third year this week. Taking place from 1 July - 31 August 2023. The festival will showcase a wide range of live art performances in various venues and outdoor spaces, featuring established artists and emerging talent. It offers a diverse cultural program including theatre, circus, opera, dance, music, outdoor arts, family shows, talks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s on in London this week: 23 – 29 September 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-23-29-september-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-23-29-september-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 23 – 29 September 2024.&#xA;Eugene Onegin&#xA;Experience the romantic drama of Tchaikovsky’s Eugene Onegin in a brand-new production by Ted Huffman. Making his Main Stage debut, Huffman explores themes of memory and desire through this classic tale. Featuring Gordon Bintner as Onegin and Kristina Mkhitaryan as Tatyana, with Henrik Nánási conducting, this production offers a fresh perspective on a timeless story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s on in London this week: 3 - 9 February 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-3-9-february-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-3-9-february-2025/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 3 - 9 February 2025.&#xA;Orchid Festival&#xA;Kew Gardens’ annual Orchid Festival has returned, celebrating Peru’s vibrant flora and fauna. The Princess of Wales Conservatory features orchids, alpacas, flamingos, and large-scale photography by Peruvian artist Mariano Vivanco, as well as murals by Lima-born Gisella Stapleton.&#xA;Date: 1 February - 2 March 2025. Location: Princess of Wales Conservatory Kew, Richmond, London, TW9 3AE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why have female leaders been so successful in handling the coronavirus pandemic?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfrsk515mq9798w8cyuh8g8fmvwwi1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfrsk515mq9798w8cyuh8g8fmvwwi1/</guid>
      <description>In the last few weeks, the UK has watched as its European neighbours have started to reopen shops, meet with family members and enjoy some semblance of life before lockdown. Like a naughty child, confined to its room, watching his friends from the window as they play outside, the UK public have become increasingly frustrated.&#xA;Although the outbreak of coronavirus is a global pandemic, nations around the world have responded differently with countries such as Germany and New Zealand having relatively more success compared to the UK, America and Brazil who have experienced the highest death tolls.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
