<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London12 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london12/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London12 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london12/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Canada Goose launch a week long takeover at Selfridges Cinema</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/canada-goose-launch-a-week-long-takeover-at-selfridges-cinema/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/canada-goose-launch-a-week-long-takeover-at-selfridges-cinema/</guid>
      <description>Sheila Atim and Clara Amfo launch the Canada Goose takeover at Selfridges Cinema, celebrating bold and brave women.&#xA;Sheila Atim and Clara Amfo launch the Canada Goose takeover at Selfridges Cinema. © Annie Knowles.&#xA;Canada Goose has launched a special cinematic takeover at Selfridges Cinema this week. The exclusive event commenced with an inaugural screening hosted by Sheila Atim, the face of the brand&amp;rsquo;s FW23 campaign, Live in the Open, and the charismatic TV presenter and broadcaster Clara Amfo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Night Sky Concert Lab is coming to St John&#39;s Smith Square</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/the-night-sky-concert-lab-is-coming-to-st-johns-smith-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/the-night-sky-concert-lab-is-coming-to-st-johns-smith-square/</guid>
      <description>The Night Sky Concert Lab is going to be at St John’s Smith Square this November for two performances – one at 7pm and one at 9pm. The show will feature music from the Southbank Sinfonia, conducted by Olivia Clarke, and will be narrated by NASA astronaut Mike Massimino, whilst images from the James Webb Telescope are displayed.&#xA;This event promises to be an immersive, sonic journey into the cosmos that has been sparking curiosity since the beginning of time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
