<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Explore Feat on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/explore-feat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Explore Feat on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/explore-feat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hart Shoreditch Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hart-shoreditch-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hart-shoreditch-review/</guid>
      <description>Hart Shoreditch, situated in the vibrant heart of Shoreditch, provides a charming and sophisticated retreat that captures the essence of the local area.&#xA;Image: Hart Shoreditch&#xA;Located in the beating heart of Shoerditch, Hart Shoreditch offers a cosy, laid back and elegant base in which to explore all the local area has to offer. Inspired by East London’s past, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique design is a celebration of Shoreditch and its heritage as a centre for craftspeople and makers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A guide to playing tennis in London</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/where-to-play-tennis-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/where-to-play-tennis-in-london/</guid>
      <description>A comprehensive guide to playing tennis in London. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for private members&amp;rsquo; courts, pay-to-play options, or free court locations. Find your perfect tennis spot in the London boroughs and start playing today!&#xA;Image: Todd Trapani&#xA;Looking for a place to play tennis in London? Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned player or have recently been inspired by Emma Raducanu&amp;rsquo;s success at the US Open, London has plenty of options to offer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best markets in London</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-markets-in-londonrqmarket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-markets-in-londonrqmarket/</guid>
      <description>The London market is at the epicentre of London life from the avid foodie to the antique collector and fashionistas alike, we all want in on the market scene. There is nothing like a Sunday afternoon trip to the market, here is our guide to the best markets in London.&#xA;Columbia Road Flower Market Columbia Road Flower Market situated in trendy Shoreditch is home to several flower stalls. You’ll find friendly traders selling buckets full of the finest cut flowers, bulbs, herbs and garden fittings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best parks in London</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-parks-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-parks-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Escaping the hectic streets of London is a necessity for many of us, whether its getting lost in a book, going for a walk, or enjoying a picnic with friends there are several activities on offer in London’s many parks. Here’s our guide to the best London parks and all you need to know when you get there.&#xA;Hyde Park Hyde Park is 350 acres of beauty located in the heart of the city, complete with beautiful man-made serpentine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford Street Christmas lights to return in November</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</guid>
      <description>Oxford Street&amp;rsquo;s dazzling Christmas lights are poised to make a grand return on 2 November, ushering in the festive spirit throughout London.&#xA;Image: Oxford Street Christmas lights to return 2 November 2023.&#xA;On 2 November, the festive season will kick off on Oxford Street as its renowned Christmas lights illuminate the iconic London street. The city&amp;rsquo;s ultimate holiday destination will shine brightly with brilliant white stars (and lots of people capturing Instagram-worthy pictures), creating that magical Christmas atmosphere we associate with London during this time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
