<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Explore Travel on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/categories/explore-travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Explore Travel on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/categories/explore-travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hart Shoreditch Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hart-shoreditch-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hart-shoreditch-review/</guid>
      <description>Hart Shoreditch, situated in the vibrant heart of Shoreditch, provides a charming and sophisticated retreat that captures the essence of the local area.&#xA;Image: Hart Shoreditch&#xA;Located in the beating heart of Shoerditch, Hart Shoreditch offers a cosy, laid back and elegant base in which to explore all the local area has to offer. Inspired by East London’s past, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique design is a celebration of Shoreditch and its heritage as a centre for craftspeople and makers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 great ideas for enjoying a last-minute holiday in Prague</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/4-great-ideas-for-enjoying-a-last-minute-holiday-in-prague/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/4-great-ideas-for-enjoying-a-last-minute-holiday-in-prague/</guid>
      <description>Discover the charms of spontaneous travel in Prague, where you can enjoy adventures amid its rich culture and scenic beauty.&#xA;Image: Charles Bridge in Prague during sunset. © Jay Ngai&#xA;Tourism in Prague is thriving, which means it&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to visit. The city collaborates with the PCT each year to promote domestic tourism and welcome tourists. According to František Cipro, director of Prague City Tourism (PCT), Prague will welcome nearly eight million visitors in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coolest locations in Zurich</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/coolest-locations-in-zurich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/coolest-locations-in-zurich/</guid>
      <description>Zurich West Representing Zurich creative hipster style, Zurich West embodies everything we love about Shoreditch with its own Swiss spin on it; in other words, it’s a good time. Head to Zurich west where you’ll find recycled freight cabins operating as shops, boutique shops and eateries under the arches at Im Viadukt and Frau Gerolds Garten. Frau Gerolds Garten is like a cool Box park complete with containers, a beer garden, boutique shops, great vibes and music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel Athens Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/four-seasons-astir-palace-hotel-athens-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/four-seasons-astir-palace-hotel-athens-review/</guid>
      <description>Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel Athens is a remarkable hotel that offers a luxurious experience and a tranquil and rejuvenating vacation.&#xA;Image: Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel, Athens, March 2023, © MTotoe&#xA;The Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel is a luxurious seaside escape located on a pine-clad peninsula in the Athenian Riviera, just 30 minutes away from the historical city centre of Athens and the Athens International Airport. With a rich history dating back to 1958, the hotel underwent a €650 million renovation in 2019 and boasts a unique blend of modern luxury and heritage.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
