<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FLO Food on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/categories/flo-food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FLO Food on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/categories/flo-food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Le Cordon Bleu to hold Summer Festival in London in July</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/le-cordon-bleu-to-hold-summer-festival-in-london-in-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/le-cordon-bleu-to-hold-summer-festival-in-london-in-july/</guid>
      <description>Le Cordon Bleu London&amp;rsquo;s Summer Festival 2023 is coming to London in July 2023 and will feature cooking demonstrations, workshops, wine tastings, and guest chef showcases by renowned culinary talents.&#xA;Image: Le Cordon Bleu London&#xA;Le Cordon Bleu London is gearing up for their highly anticipated annual Summer Festival, set to be held at their institute in Bloomsbury. Taking place on 1 July 2023, the festival promises a delightful array of activities to entice culinary enthusiasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLODown: Pizzeria Mozza</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-pizzeria-mozza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-pizzeria-mozza/</guid>
      <description>Image: @pizza_diaries_ldn&#xA;It’s been a while since I’ve been on the pizza trail, or rather the pizza-in-actual-establishments trail. I was delighted when @marinagpoloughlin writing a sterling review of a new LA pizzeria in Oxford Circus coincided with my company opening an office nearby. Having excitedly told anyone I’d encountered at the office opening about my desire to try this (whilst letting them know I have a pizza blog), I managed to drag a few colleagues out of the local pubs and into the pizzeria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: Boca Cha Cha</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flo-london-favourites-boca-cha-cha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flo-london-favourites-boca-cha-cha/</guid>
      <description>What’s the deal ? Boca Cha Cha is an eccentric bohemian café and restaurant tucked away in Little Venice. With an eclectic mash-up of velvet sofas, disco balls, wicker armchairs, neon lights and chandeliers, and contemporary art the décor is as much a draw as the food. Boca Cha Cha brings together a fusion of Mexican, Mediterranean, and Spanish foods, from cheese and truffle croquet with poached egg to French toast with dulce de leche and berries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: top 5 in food this week</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</guid>
      <description>We are into the fourth week of the government’s new ‘Eat Out to Help Out!’ scheme. It came into effect on 3 August and lasts till the end of the month, giving people 50% off their bill at thousands of restaurants across the country on Mondays, Tuesdays and Wednesdays. The scheme is designed to encourage us all to get out there and support the hospitality industry following the nationwide lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best restaurants to eat light and wholesome food in London</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Discover London&amp;rsquo;s top destinations for light, nutritious, and wholesome food with our guide. From the ever-popular vegetarian favourite KIN Cafe to the renowned Maggie Jones&amp;rsquo;s, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a range of options to satisfy your cravings.&#xA;Image: Dan Gold&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a dining experience in London that is both delicious and nutritious, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. Our six restaurant recommendations offer a delightful selection of light, flavourful meals that are not only wholesome but also leave you feeling energised and fully satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highroad Social: Greenwich’s newest restaurant has hit the dining scene</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/highroad-social-greenwich-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/highroad-social-greenwich-review/</guid>
      <description>On a sunny Friday we decided to make a day of it and journey to Greenwich from West London. We set off from Putney Pier via Uber Boat for the 90-minute trip to Greenwich to be tourists for the day in our beloved city. It is rather wonderful seeing the city from the water going under iconic bridges such as Albert Bridge, Westminster Bridge, Millennium Bridge and Tower Bridge and passing some iconic London Landmarks; Battersea Power Station, Houses of Parliament, Big Ben, the Millennium Wheel, The Shard, Tate Modern, Tower of London and the stunning modern skyline of the Square Mile and eventually all the old shipping wharfs as we neared our destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOZI Restaurant Victoria Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</guid>
      <description>TOZI, derived from the affectionate Venetian slang for “a close-knit group of friends,” is the brainchild of an Italian trio that met while opening Shoreditch House under the Soho House Group. In 2013, Chef Maurilio Molteni, fresh from his time as Head Chef at Shoreditch House and developing the menu at Cecconi’s, opened the first TOZI restaurant in London. He was joined by Stefano Meloni and Marco Bullegas as restaurant manager and bar manager, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegan food is not just for January, it’s for life</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/vegan-food-is-not-just-for-january-its-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/vegan-food-is-not-just-for-january-its-for-life/</guid>
      <description>It was both extremely satisfying and hugely depressing to me that January ended on a Sunday this year. It looks lovely in the calendar but meant a long stretch till I could eat some cheese. I think it was actually really motivating to have something to focus on and pour my energy into considering the current lockdown, and I would actually recommend setting yourself a goal like this for the weeks moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to find London&#39;s best ice cream parlours this summer 2024</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>London’s summer weather may be unpredictable, but its ice cream parlours are always ready for sunny days. From the return of Anya Hindmarch’s Ice Cream Project to delicious soft serve in Chinatown and neighbourhood favourite Udderlicious, here are some of our top spots to enjoy ice cream in London this summer.&#xA;The Ice Cream Project III Anya Hindmarch ice cream project III. Photo by MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Returning for its third year, The Ice Cream Project is back at The Village from 7 June to 18 August, offering unexpectedly delicious ice creams and sorbets inspired by Anya Hindmarch&amp;rsquo;s favourite cult food brands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
