<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artnews3 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/artnews3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artnews3 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/artnews3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A group exhibition featuring nine contemporary artists opens at Pictorum Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-group-exhibition-featuring-nine-contemporary-artists-opens-at-pictorum-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-group-exhibition-featuring-nine-contemporary-artists-opens-at-pictorum-gallery/</guid>
      <description>‘Only Until This Cigarette is Ended’, a group exhibition by nine contemporary artists, offers a multifaceted exploration of collective memory and reflection at Pictorum Gallery.&#xA;Image: Only Until This Cigarette is Ended exhibition at Pictorum Gallery. Image courtesy of Pictorum Gallery.&#xA;A group exhibition, Only Until This Cigarette is Ended, has opened at Pictorum Gallery, showcasing the works of nine international artists. Among them are Leily Moghtader Mojdehi, Tosin Kalejaye, Naomi Boiko, Olamide Ogunade, Elena Rivera-Montanes, Verde, Nina Baxter, Johanna Bath, and Brittany Fanning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOLAIRE CULTURE, An Exhibition Celebrating 250 Years of Veuve Clicquot will open in London in May 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/solaire-culture-an-exhibition-celebrating-250-years-of-veuve-clicquot-will-open-in-london-in-may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/solaire-culture-an-exhibition-celebrating-250-years-of-veuve-clicquot-will-open-in-london-in-may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Veuve Clicquot announces today the next chapter of the highly successful global exhibition, SOLAIRE CULTURE, to celebrate 250 years of the iconic house. After debuting in Tokyo and Los Angeles in 2022, the exhibition is travelling to London, to take over Piccadilly Circus in May 2023.&#xA;Image: Veuve Clicquot “Solaire Culture” exhibition, Yayoi Kusama, Tokyo, 2022&#xA;SOLAIRE CULTURE celebrates Veuve Clicquot&amp;rsquo;s 250 years of history, focusing on the legacy of Madame Clicquot, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s first female entrepreneurs who took over the reins of the house in 1805, and the contemporary vision of the curator, Camille Morineau, and designer Constance Guisset.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
