<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in June in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>June in London is buzzing with excitement as festival season kicks off and some much-loved events return. From Southbank Centre&amp;rsquo;s Meltdown festival, curated by the legendary Chaka Khan, to the delightful lunchtime Jazz Series at Cadogan Hall. Add in the Sundance Film Festival and the revival of Open Water Swimming, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got a month packed with fantastic activities. Here&amp;rsquo;s our selection of things to do in London this June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to find public art in London right now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-public-art-in-london-this-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-public-art-in-london-this-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>Summer in London offers the perfect opportunity to delve into the city&amp;rsquo;s fantastic public art trails. With the resurgence of public art programmes at The Southbank Centre, alongside the public art trail associated with Chelsea and Kensington Art Week, as well as permanent fixtures like The Line in East London and the last opportunity to view sculptures from the 12th edition of Sculptures in the City, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty to explore. Here&amp;rsquo;s our guide on when and where to experience free public art in London this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: The Nest Rooftop Bar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-the-nest-rooftop-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-the-nest-rooftop-bar/</guid>
      <description>Image: MTotoe&#xA;The Nest is a welcome addition to London’s plethora of rooftop bars and is located just a short walk from Oxford Circus station. The bar sits on the 16th floor of the Treehouse Hotel which opened just under a year ago. It’s a quirky, green haven filled with wooden furniture and a wraparound terrace, offering 360-degree views of the city.&#xA;Whilst the food menu isn&amp;rsquo;t particularly extensive, think small plates and light snacks, they do have a great selection of cocktails to make up for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: this week in art (13th- 15th March 2020)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-this-week-in-art-13th-15th-march-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-this-week-in-art-13th-15th-march-2020/</guid>
      <description>The Affordable Art Fair Illustration: Affordable Art Fair&#xA;When?&#xA;12th March- 15th March&#xA;Price?&#xA;£9-27&#xA;#FLODown: The spring edition of the Affordable Art Fair lands in Battersea Park this weekend. The fair will feature contemporary artworks priced between £50-£6000 from 100s of galleries from all over the globe. Expect to find a plethora of workshops, talks and tours, plus this will be a fantastic opportunity to get your hands on some great art pieces at affordable prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: top 5 in food this week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</guid>
      <description>We are into the fourth week of the government’s new ‘Eat Out to Help Out!’ scheme. It came into effect on 3 August and lasts till the end of the month, giving people 50% off their bill at thousands of restaurants across the country on Mondays, Tuesdays and Wednesdays. The scheme is designed to encourage us all to get out there and support the hospitality industry following the nationwide lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London’s best indoor green spaces to escape the winter blues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</guid>
      <description>When the winter chill sets in and the London skies are often grey and rainy, indoor green spaces offer the perfect escape. From towering tropical plants to lush Victorian conservatories, here are some of the most remarkable indoor gardens to visit in London, providing a serene environment for relaxation and inspiration, no matter the weather.&#xA;Barbican Conservatory Barbican Conservatory, Barbican Centre. © MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Step into a hidden world of exotic plants and trees at the Barbican Conservatory, a tropical oasis nestled within the iconic Barbican Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The London Diaries: the copywriter living at home</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/london-diaries-25-30k-in-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/london-diaries-25-30k-in-the-city/</guid>
      <description>Job: Copywriter&#xA;Time living in London: Prior to the COVID-19 pandemic, I lived in London Bridge and then Waterloo for a year. Now I live at home with my mum.&#xA;Area: Sutton&#xA;Pay range: £25,000 - £30,000&#xA;Relationship status: Single&#xA;Rent: £100 – a token gesture.&#xA;Monday Due to the pandemic, I’ve been working from home since March which has been a great opportunity to get extensive wear out of my pyjamas and gym gear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in November 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</guid>
      <description>November in London marks the return of many beloved Christmas traditions across the city. Highlights include the switching on of Christmas lights and the return of festive ice skating at Somerset House. Music enthusiasts can enjoy celebrations for 30 years of Bugged Out! at Drumsheds, along with performances of Hansel and Gretel at the Royal Opera House. The art scene will be vibrant with the opening of several new exhibitions, including an exploration of photography in Britain during the 80s at Tate Britain, as well as the return of the Woolwich Contemporary Print Fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in October 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</guid>
      <description>October has arrived and London is back, and there are heaps of great events on. With Halloween events back in full swing, Black History Month and some of the best in arts and culture including Southbank’s London Literature Festival and Frieze London, it’s shaping up to be a big one!&#xA;Here are some of our favourite things you can do in the city this October.&#xA;Affordable Art Fair Battersea Autumn When: 20 – 23 October 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London this weekend: 8-10 March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this weekend: 8 –10 March 2024.&#xA;New York City Ballet (NYCB)&#xA;New York City Ballet, founded in 1948 by George Balanchine and Lincoln Kirstein, is renowned for its blend of contemporary creations and classic choreographies. Their upcoming performance in the UK presents a rare opportunity to witness the company&amp;rsquo;s world-class talent. The repertoire includes Justin Peck&amp;rsquo;s Rotunda, featuring a commissioned score by Nico Muhly, Duo Concertant by Balanchine, Pam Tanowitz&amp;rsquo;s Gustave le Gray No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to find London&#39;s best ice cream parlours this summer 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>London’s summer weather may be unpredictable, but its ice cream parlours are always ready for sunny days. From the return of Anya Hindmarch’s Ice Cream Project to delicious soft serve in Chinatown and neighbourhood favourite Udderlicious, here are some of our top spots to enjoy ice cream in London this summer.&#xA;The Ice Cream Project III Anya Hindmarch ice cream project III. Photo by MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Returning for its third year, The Ice Cream Project is back at The Village from 7 June to 18 August, offering unexpectedly delicious ice creams and sorbets inspired by Anya Hindmarch&amp;rsquo;s favourite cult food brands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
