<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Londonlate on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/londonlate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Londonlate on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/londonlate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Nimrod Vardi and Claudel Goy, directors of arebyte gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nimrod-vardi-and-claudel-goy-the-directors-of-arebyte-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nimrod-vardi-and-claudel-goy-the-directors-of-arebyte-gallery/</guid>
      <description>“To us, immersive doesn’t just mean 360° projections or putting on a VR headset. It means telling a story that invites people in, that shifts their perception, and brings them along for the journey.”&#xA;- Nimrod Vardi&#xA;Nimrod Vardi and Claudel Goy, the Directors of arebyte gallery&#xA;Venturing outside the usual Central London art stomping grounds can sometimes feel like an effort. But often, it is really worth it. Case in point for arebyte Gallery, currently based on London City Island (but moving all their programming to Camden soon).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindokuhle Sobekwa wins 2025 Deutsche Börse Photography Foundation Prize</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lindokuhle-sobekwa-wins-2025-deutsche-brse-photography-foundation-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lindokuhle-sobekwa-wins-2025-deutsche-brse-photography-foundation-prize/</guid>
      <description>Lindokuhle Sobekwa honoured for powerful tribute to his late sister and a poignant reflection on South Africa’s social history.&#xA;Lindokuhle Sobekwa. The Photographers’ Gallery. Deutsche Börse Photography Foundation Prize 2025. Image credit Heather Shuker.&#xA;South African photographer Lindokuhle Sobekwa has been awarded the 2025 Deutsche Börse Photography Foundation Prize for his personal photobook I carry Her photo with Me. The £30,000 prize, announced on 15 May at The Photographers’ Gallery in London by author and photographer Caleb Azumah Nelson, celebrates the most significant contribution to international contemporary photography over the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Much Ado About Nothing, Shakespeare&#39;s Globe Theatre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/much-ado-about-nothing-shakespeares-globe-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/much-ado-about-nothing-shakespeares-globe-review/</guid>
      <description>The Globe’s 2024 summer season is off to a flying start with a joyous romp through one of Shakespeare’s much-loved comedies.&#xA;Ekow Quartey as Benedick and Amalia Vitale as Beatrice. Photography by Marc Brenner.&#xA;Sean Holmes’ production of Much Ado About Nothing is the kind of Shakespeare GCSE English teachers dream about. We are transported to the warm and hazy summer days of sixteenth century Italy, where trees are laden with ripening oranges, noblemen stroll through sun-dappled orchards and evenings are filled with the lively intricacies of dances and music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in June in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>June in London is buzzing with excitement as festival season kicks off and some much-loved events return. From Southbank Centre&amp;rsquo;s Meltdown festival, curated by the legendary Chaka Khan, to the delightful lunchtime Jazz Series at Cadogan Hall. Add in the Sundance Film Festival and the revival of Open Water Swimming, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got a month packed with fantastic activities. Here&amp;rsquo;s our selection of things to do in London this June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterclass, Southbank Centre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/masterclass-southbank-centre-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/masterclass-southbank-centre-review/</guid>
      <description>The ‘Mr Nasty of American Theatre’ gets his comeuppance in this comedic dissection of the white male artist, which lifts the lid on issues that continue to plague the creative industries.&#xA;Irish theatre company Brokentalkers and artist Adrienne Truscott. make their London debut at the Southbank Centre with Masterclass. Photo by Ste Murray.&#xA;Following a hit international tour, Irish theatre company Brokentalkers and artist Adrienne Truscott make their London debut at the Southbank Centre with Masterclass, a witty examination of gender and power in the arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A guide to events not to miss at London Craft Week 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/events-not-to-miss-at-london-craft-week-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/events-not-to-miss-at-london-craft-week-2024/</guid>
      <description>London Craft Week 2024 returns this week for its 10th edition, running from 13 - 19 May 2024, highlighting British and international creativity by showcasing over 750 established and emerging makers, designers, brands, and galleries. The festival offers a curated selection of events that promise to inspire and help you discover some of the great talent right on our doorstep! Here are eight notable events to explore during London Craft Week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLODown: Pizzeria Mozza</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flodown-pizzeria-mozza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flodown-pizzeria-mozza/</guid>
      <description>Image: @pizza_diaries_ldn&#xA;It’s been a while since I’ve been on the pizza trail, or rather the pizza-in-actual-establishments trail. I was delighted when @marinagpoloughlin writing a sterling review of a new LA pizzeria in Oxford Circus coincided with my company opening an office nearby. Having excitedly told anyone I’d encountered at the office opening about my desire to try this (whilst letting them know I have a pizza blog), I managed to drag a few colleagues out of the local pubs and into the pizzeria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: top 5 in food this week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-top-5-in-food-this-week/</guid>
      <description>We are into the fourth week of the government’s new ‘Eat Out to Help Out!’ scheme. It came into effect on 3 August and lasts till the end of the month, giving people 50% off their bill at thousands of restaurants across the country on Mondays, Tuesdays and Wednesdays. The scheme is designed to encourage us all to get out there and support the hospitality industry following the nationwide lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 unmissable art fairs and events in London for 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/22-unmissable-art-fairs-and-events-in-london-for-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/22-unmissable-art-fairs-and-events-in-london-for-2025/</guid>
      <description>This year, London will host an array of art fairs, art weeks, and design festivals, showcasing everything from photography and contemporary art to ceramics, antiques, sculpture, and innovative design. The 2025 art scene will be as vibrant as ever, featuring long-established events like Frieze, LAPADA, and the London Design Festival, as well as exciting newcomers such as Fresh: Art Fair and the return of the London Design Biennale. With various art weeks, including Clerkenwell Design Week, also on the calendar, here’s a guide to twenty-two unmissable art fairs, events, and festivals in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 art exhibitions to see in London during Frieze Week 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/50-art-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-during-frieze-week-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/50-art-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-during-frieze-week-2024/</guid>
      <description>London’s most anticipated art month is on the horizon, with Frieze London and Masters returning to The Regent’s Park from 9 - 13 October 2024. This renowned week typically sees a flurry of activity across the city, with numerous art fairs, events, and exhibitions showcasing the best in contemporary and historical art. To help you navigate the excitement, here is your guide to 50 art exhibitions not to be missed during Frieze Week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A guide to playing tennis in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-play-tennis-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-play-tennis-in-london/</guid>
      <description>A comprehensive guide to playing tennis in London. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for private members&amp;rsquo; courts, pay-to-play options, or free court locations. Find your perfect tennis spot in the London boroughs and start playing today!&#xA;Image: Todd Trapani&#xA;Looking for a place to play tennis in London? Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned player or have recently been inspired by Emma Raducanu&amp;rsquo;s success at the US Open, London has plenty of options to offer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A guide to the most beautiful historic houses to visit in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-guide-to-the-most-beautiful-historic-homes-to-visit-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-guide-to-the-most-beautiful-historic-homes-to-visit-in-london/</guid>
      <description>London boasts an array of remarkable historic homes, each offering a unique glimpse into different eras. From classic Tudor dwellings to elegant Georgian townhouses and residences that provide insights into the Victorian era, there&amp;rsquo;s a diverse selection to explore. Whether you adore exquisite interiors or are intrigued by history and artistic masterpieces, here is our guide to beautiful historic houses to visit in London.&#xA;Sir John Soane&amp;rsquo;s Museum Sir John Soane&amp;rsquo;s Museum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahmed Mater: Chronicles at Christie&#39;s London review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ahmed-mater-chronicles-at-christies-london-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ahmed-mater-chronicles-at-christies-london-review/</guid>
      <description>Christie’s has a wonderful summer treat for us all with their exhibition for the summer featuring Ahmed Mater, a leading Saudi Contemporary Artist. This exhibition, to date, is the most comprehensive dedicated to Ahmed Mater. I have become acutely aware my knowledge of artists from Asia and the Middle East is greatly lacking and I found this free exhibition to be a wonderful introduction which I am sure will propel me to seek out more work of artists from these regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art exhibitions opening in London in January 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-opening-in-london-in-january-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-opening-in-london-in-january-2024/</guid>
      <description>While January sees the closure of several art exhibitions, it also brings the excitement of new and returning showcases. The Bloomberg New Contemporaries returns to the Camden Arts Centre, Somerset House hosts an exhibition dedicated to &amp;lsquo;cuteness,&amp;rsquo; and the London Art Fair makes its comeback. Here&amp;rsquo;s a sneak peek at the upcoming art exhibitions opening in the city this January. Fresh off the Christmas festivities, what better way to shake off the January blues than by diving into fantastic art experiences?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art exhibitions to watch out for in London in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-to-watch-out-for-in-london-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-to-watch-out-for-in-london-in-2025/</guid>
      <description>Announcements are already rolling in for London’s 2025 art exhibitions, and the line-up is shaping up splendidly. Highlights include the UK’s first exhibition dedicated to José María Velasco, Mexico’s acclaimed 19th-century painter, and the Royal Academy’s Brasil! Brasil! The Birth of Modernism, featuring over 130 works by ten prominent Brazilian artists. The newly opened V&amp;amp;A East Museum will debut The Music Is Black: A British Story, while next year will also bring two major Van Gogh exhibitions—one at the National Gallery and another at the Royal Academy of Arts, where Anselm Kiefer’s work will be shown in dialogue with Van Gogh’s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best green spaces to visit in London in summer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-green-spaces-to-visit-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-green-spaces-to-visit-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Among our passions for art and exploring bakeries, we also cherish London&amp;rsquo;s green spaces. From vast areas like the Walthamstow Wetlands to hidden gems like Phoenix Gardens and Mount Street Gardens, there&amp;rsquo;s a wealth of tranquil spots waiting to be explored. Here are our top choices of green spaces to fully embrace London&amp;rsquo;s summer in 2024.&#xA;Phoenix Garden Phoenix Garden, St Giles. Photo by MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Tucked away behind the Phoenix Theatre in St Giles, the Phoenix Garden offers a peaceful haven in the midst of busy Soho and Covent Garden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best restaurants to eat light and wholesome food in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Discover London&amp;rsquo;s top destinations for light, nutritious, and wholesome food with our guide. From the ever-popular vegetarian favourite KIN Cafe to the renowned Maggie Jones&amp;rsquo;s, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a range of options to satisfy your cravings.&#xA;Image: Dan Gold&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a dining experience in London that is both delicious and nutritious, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. Our six restaurant recommendations offer a delightful selection of light, flavourful meals that are not only wholesome but also leave you feeling energised and fully satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada Goose launch a week long takeover at Selfridges Cinema</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/canada-goose-launch-a-week-long-takeover-at-selfridges-cinema/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/canada-goose-launch-a-week-long-takeover-at-selfridges-cinema/</guid>
      <description>Sheila Atim and Clara Amfo launch the Canada Goose takeover at Selfridges Cinema, celebrating bold and brave women.&#xA;Sheila Atim and Clara Amfo launch the Canada Goose takeover at Selfridges Cinema. © Annie Knowles.&#xA;Canada Goose has launched a special cinematic takeover at Selfridges Cinema this week. The exclusive event commenced with an inaugural screening hosted by Sheila Atim, the face of the brand&amp;rsquo;s FW23 campaign, Live in the Open, and the charismatic TV presenter and broadcaster Clara Amfo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canary Wharf’s Winter Lights Festival to return in January 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/canary-wharfs-winter-lights-festival-to-return-january-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/canary-wharfs-winter-lights-festival-to-return-january-2025/</guid>
      <description>London’s dazzling Winter Lights festival returns with 11 new installations and iconic displays, transforming Canary Wharf from 21 January 2025.&#xA;The Clew by Ottotto&#xA;Canary Wharf’s Winter Lights festival returns this January for its ninth edition, bringing with it a blend of light-based art installations from both renowned and emerging artists worldwide. The free, annual event has become a much-anticipated fixture for Londoners and visitors alike, as the neighbourhood is transformed into a vibrant, luminous wonderland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIANA The Untold and Untrue Story at the King&#39;s Head Theatre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-the-untold-and-untrue-story-at-the-kings-head-theatre-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-the-untold-and-untrue-story-at-the-kings-head-theatre-review/</guid>
      <description>After a sold-out Edinburgh Fringe run in 2023 and winning the OffFest Award for Best Play, Diana - The Untold and Untrue Story has arrived in London for a three-week run at the King’s Head Theatre in Islington. Let me start by saying it is the best and silliest kind of fun and the most I’ve laughed in such a short space of time. Book it!&#xA;Diana the Untrue and Untold Story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover exceptional jazz at Ladbroke Hall this April</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-month-of-exceptional-jazz-at-ladbroke-hall-this-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-month-of-exceptional-jazz-at-ladbroke-hall-this-april/</guid>
      <description>This April, Ladbroke Hall’s renowned Friday Jazz &amp;amp; Dinner series returns, showcasing an impressive roster of artists at its Sunbeam Theatre. Each evening pairs exceptional live jazz with a carefully crafted menu from the award-winning Pollini restaurant. With tickets priced at £15 for standing and £30 for table seating, the series offers an intimate setting to enjoy world-class music in the heart of West London.&#xA;© Ladbroke Hall&#xA;The month opens on 4 April with saxophonist Alex Garnett, who will be joined by Will Barry (piano), Ferg Ireland (double bass), and Will Cleasby (drums).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLO London x British Vogue 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flo-london-x-british-vogue-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flo-london-x-british-vogue-2022/</guid>
      <description>FLO London features in the June, July and August 2022 issues of British Vogue. As a female-owned business this has been a wonderful opportunity and a chance to showcase our newest collection of Ghanaian wax print products made from Nsubra fabrics.&#xA;“I created FLO London The Shop with the intent of relaying the meanings and beauty of some of the wonderful Ghanaian wax print fabrics I have been in awe of my whole life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highroad Social: Greenwich’s newest restaurant has hit the dining scene</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/highroad-social-greenwich-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/highroad-social-greenwich-review/</guid>
      <description>On a sunny Friday we decided to make a day of it and journey to Greenwich from West London. We set off from Putney Pier via Uber Boat for the 90-minute trip to Greenwich to be tourists for the day in our beloved city. It is rather wonderful seeing the city from the water going under iconic bridges such as Albert Bridge, Westminster Bridge, Millennium Bridge and Tower Bridge and passing some iconic London Landmarks; Battersea Power Station, Houses of Parliament, Big Ben, the Millennium Wheel, The Shard, Tate Modern, Tower of London and the stunning modern skyline of the Square Mile and eventually all the old shipping wharfs as we neared our destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitality In The Woods festival 2023 review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-festival-2023-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-festival-2023-review/</guid>
      <description>Hospitality in the Woods festival makes a triumphant return to London.&#xA;Image: Hospitality In The Woods 2023. Beckhenham Palace Park. © Trade Photographer.&#xA;Leaving the tram at Beckenham Junction, you’d have been hard pressed to believe there was anything significant going on in the town on Saturday as dog walkers and brunchers milled about, basking in the glorious summer weather. However, just a short walk away, Beckenham Place Park welcomed a sea of bucket hats and became home to one of the most recognisable festival in Drum &amp;amp; Bass for the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Judith Clark</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-judith-clark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-judith-clark/</guid>
      <description>“I love the discipline of exhibiting fashion as much as I did 30 years ago. It never exhausts itself for me …”&#xA;- Judith Clark&#xA;Portrait of Judith Clark, UAL. Photo: Loro Piana**.**&#xA;Judith Clark is a curator and fashion exhibition-maker, and currently Professor of Fashion and Museology at the University of the Arts London. She lectures on the MA Fashion Curation and is a founding Director of the Centre for Fashion Curation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Oskar Zięta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-oskar-zieta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-oskar-zieta/</guid>
      <description>“When you love what you do, you are determined to achieve the intended goal - the creative process becomes a part of you.”&#xA;- Oskar Zięta&#xA;Oskar Zięta&#xA;Oskar Zięta, architect, process designer and artist, works across disciplines to explore the intersections of form, material and technology. His practice combines design, engineering, art and bionics to produce objects that push the limits of metal and its potential. Using a technique he developed called FiDU, Zięta inflates thin steel sheets with air, shaping them into durable, lightweight structures with a strong sculptural presence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Varvara Roza</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-varvara-roza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-varvara-roza/</guid>
      <description>“…I am genuinely committed to the promotion of artists whose work is utterly integral to the landscape of contemporary art, because art, to me, is so much more than an asset class&amp;hellip;”&#xA;- Varvara Roza&#xA;Varvara Roza.&#xA;Working from core values of trust and commitment, Varvara Roza is an increasingly renowned private art advisor and artist representative on the London scene whose verve and passion for bringing leading contemporary artists to the global stage is second to none.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jasleen Kaur wins Turner Prize 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/jasleen-kaur-wins-turner-prize-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/jasleen-kaur-wins-turner-prize-2024/</guid>
      <description>Jasleen Kaur wins the 2024 Turner Prize for her exploration of culture, identity, and resilience through sound, music, and everyday objects.&#xA;Turner Prize 2024 Ceremony Tate Britain 3 December 2024 Credit David Parry, PA Media Assignments.&#xA;Jasleen Kaur has been named the winner of the prestigious Turner Prize 2024, earning the £25,000 award. The announcement was made during a live ceremony at Tate Britain, hosted by actor James Norton and broadcast on the BBC News channel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London’s best indoor green spaces to escape the winter blues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</guid>
      <description>When the winter chill sets in and the London skies are often grey and rainy, indoor green spaces offer the perfect escape. From towering tropical plants to lush Victorian conservatories, here are some of the most remarkable indoor gardens to visit in London, providing a serene environment for relaxation and inspiration, no matter the weather.&#xA;Barbican Conservatory Barbican Conservatory, Barbican Centre. © MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Step into a hidden world of exotic plants and trees at the Barbican Conservatory, a tropical oasis nestled within the iconic Barbican Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Gallery Van Gogh exhibition to open 24 hours</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/national-gallery-van-gogh-exhibition-to-open-24-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/national-gallery-van-gogh-exhibition-to-open-24-hours/</guid>
      <description>The National Gallery will open overnight on 17 January 2025, for the final weekend of its sell-out exhibition, Van Gogh: Poets and Lovers.&#xA;Vincent van Gogh Sunflowers, 1888; oil on canvas 92.1 × 73 cm, Bought, Courtauld Fund, 1924, © The National Gallery, London.&#xA;As the critically acclaimed Van Gogh: Poets and Lovers exhibition at the National Gallery approaches its final days, the Gallery will open its doors all night on Friday 17 January 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NELKEN a piece by Pina Bausch at Sadler&#39;s Wells review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-nelken-a-piece-by-pina-bausch-at-sadlers-wells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-nelken-a-piece-by-pina-bausch-at-sadlers-wells/</guid>
      <description>Appropriately after Valentine’s Day we are sitting above a stage carpeted with 8000 carnations to see NELKEN by Tanztheater Wuppertal Pina Bausch + Terrain Boris Charmatz performing on a stage at the Sadler’s Wells Theatre. This seminal piece debuted in 1982 and hasn’t been seen here since 2005. It returns now with a new generation of dancers and under its new artistic director of 18 months, Boris Charmatz.&#xA;Nelken. © Oliver Look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford Street Christmas lights to return in November</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</guid>
      <description>Oxford Street&amp;rsquo;s dazzling Christmas lights are poised to make a grand return on 2 November, ushering in the festive spirit throughout London.&#xA;Image: Oxford Street Christmas lights to return 2 November 2023.&#xA;On 2 November, the festive season will kick off on Oxford Street as its renowned Christmas lights illuminate the iconic London street. The city&amp;rsquo;s ultimate holiday destination will shine brightly with brilliant white stars (and lots of people capturing Instagram-worthy pictures), creating that magical Christmas atmosphere we associate with London during this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pauline Loctin&#39;s ‘Flying in Nuanced Colours’ to debut at Uncommon Holborn for London Design Festival 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pauline-loctin-installation-to-debut-at-uncommon-holborn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pauline-loctin-installation-to-debut-at-uncommon-holborn/</guid>
      <description>Uncommon Holborn to present Pauline Loctin’s ‘Flying in Nuanced Colours’— a major paper sculpture installation for London Design Festival in September.&#xA;Pauline Loctin x Uncommon Holborn. Photo by Mark Cocksedge.&#xA;This September, Uncommon Holborn will host Flying in Nuanced Colours, a striking installation by renowned paper sculptor Pauline Loctin, as part of London Design Festival 2024. The exhibition, a bespoke commission for the B Corp certified workspace provider, merges traditional origami with modern art to create a captivating visual experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photography exhibitions to see in London now and in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/photography-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-now-and-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/photography-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-now-and-in-2025/</guid>
      <description>London is currently hosting an array of photography exhibitions offering compelling reflections on nature, identity, and urban life — with even more set to open in the later stages of 2025. From Wildlife Photographer of the Year at the Natural History Museum, which highlights the beauty and fragility of the natural world, to Gabriel Moses’ exhibition at 180 Studios, showcasing his work across fashion, music, and sport. The Photographers’ Gallery offers a glimpse into the changing landscape of Leeds with a Peter Mitchell retrospective, while Nature Study at the V&amp;amp;A explores ecological themes through the contemporary photobook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printworks London closure: the venue whose spirit lives on</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/printworks-closure-the-venue-whose-spirit-lives-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/printworks-closure-the-venue-whose-spirit-lives-on/</guid>
      <description>The closure of Printworks marks the end of an era for London&amp;rsquo;s clubbing scene, but the legacy of this iconic venue will undoubtedly live on.&#xA;Image: Closing weekend at Printworks London. © Emma Chadwick&#xA;It was a sad weekend for London’s ravers as the iconic Printworks nightclub closed its doors for the last time. Artists including Peggy Gou, Sub Focus and Black Coffee gathered in the press halls for a final send-off, creating the fantastic atmosphere and energy that the venue is known and loved for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: 13th Edition of Sculpture in the City 2024, City of London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/13th-edition-of-sculpture-in-the-city-2024-city-of-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/13th-edition-of-sculpture-in-the-city-2024-city-of-london/</guid>
      <description>We were keen to receive an invitation to tour this year’s 13th Edition of Sculpture in the City. There is something about public sculpture, which is extremely appealing, with each sculpture displayed with its own unique back drop and surroundings and the opportunity of accidental interaction with the art.&#xA;Temple, Richard Mackness, part of the 13th edition of Sculpture in the City. © Richard Mackness. Photo © Nick Turpin.&#xA;Having lived in Sydney for 13 years Sculpture by the Sea (begins mid-October) was one of my favourite events of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL, Mohamed Jabaly, SAFAR Film Festival</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-life-is-beautiful-mohamed-jabaly-safar-film-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-life-is-beautiful-mohamed-jabaly-safar-film-festival/</guid>
      <description>The opening documentary of this year’s SAFAR Film Festival is a moving, first-person account of Mohamed Jabaly’s experience of travelling abroad and finding himself stranded, unable to return to his home in Gaza, forced to watch war unfold through his phone screen, and the community that forms around him as he fights to remain in a country that considers him stateless.&#xA;Life Is Beautiful.&#xA;Palestine is at the heart of this year’s SAFAR Film Festival, the largest festival in the UK dedicated to cinema from the Arab world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: We wear our wheels with pride by Robyn Orlin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</guid>
      <description>I have arrived at the last of the four Van Cleef &amp;amp; Arpel Dance Reflection evenings I chose to review, and I am now wishing I had the energy and time see every show of this contemporary dance festival. It has been a wonderfully diverse showcase, and it seems I saved the most joyous for last.&#xA;The full title of this piece—WE WEAR OUR WHEELS WITH PRIDE AND SLAP YOUR STREET WITH COLOR&amp;hellip; WE SAID “BONJOUR” TO SATAN IN 1820—is a homage to the rickshaw drivers of Durban by South African choreographer, Robyn Orlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Academy Summer Exhibition 2025 review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</guid>
      <description>Arriving right on cue with the first wafts of summer London heat, the Royal Academy Summer Show has returned for its 257th exhibition. Curated under the theme of ‘Dialogues,’ the 2025 edition is coordinated by internationally acclaimed architect and Royal Academician Farshid Moussavi and explores art’s capacity to forge dialogues and build sensitivity towards societal concerns such as ecology, survival and living together. As Moussavi explained: “These dialogues can be between people of different races, genders, or cultures; between humans, all species, and the planet; or across different disciplines - art, science, politics for example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serpentine Gallery presents major new public sculpture by Gerhard Richter in Kensington Gardens</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/serpentine-gallery-presents-major-new-public-sculpture-by-gerhard-richters-in-kensington-gardens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/serpentine-gallery-presents-major-new-public-sculpture-by-gerhard-richters-in-kensington-gardens/</guid>
      <description>Renowned artist Gerhard Richter&amp;rsquo;s monumental sculpture, STRIP-TOWER (2023) unveiled at Serpentine South.&#xA;STRIP-TOWER (2023) by Gerhard Richter © 2024, Gerhard Richter, Prudence Cuming Associates.&#xA;Serpentine Galleries, in collaboration with The Royal Parks, is set to unveil a monumental new sculpture by renowned German artist Gerhard Richter. Entitled STRIP-TOWER (2023), this impressive piece will be showcased at Serpentine South in Kensington Gardens from 25 April - 27 October 2024. This unveiling marks the continuation of a tradition dating back to Serpentine&amp;rsquo;s establishment in 1970, of presenting significant public artworks within the Royal Parks, offering visitors an opportunity to engage with art amidst the natural beauty of London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southbank Centre’s new Festival “Multitudes” to open in April 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/southbank-centres-new-festival-multitudes-to-open-in-april-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/southbank-centres-new-festival-multitudes-to-open-in-april-2025/</guid>
      <description>Multitudes at Southbank Centre will reimagine live music through bold collaborations across dance, theatre, and visual arts.&#xA;LPO x Circa: Daphnis and Chloe. © Laura Manariti.&#xA;Multitudes is an exciting new arts festival taking place at the Southbank Centre from 23 April to 3 May 2025. This festival reimagines the concert hall experience by blending orchestral music with a wide range of artistic disciplines, including dance, performance, spoken word, and visual arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanqueray No. TEN launches ‘Make It a TEN’ Residency at Artesian</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tanqueray-no-ten-launches-make-it-a-ten-residency-at-artesian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tanqueray-no-ten-launches-make-it-a-ten-residency-at-artesian/</guid>
      <description>Stanley Tucci and head bartender Giulia Cuccurullo present a curated cocktail experience at Artesian, located in The Langham Hotel, in celebration of London Cocktail Week.&#xA;Stanley Tucci and head bartender Giulia Cuccurullo present a curated cocktail experience at Artesian, in celebration of London Cocktail Week from 3 - 31 October 2024.&#xA;In celebration of London Cocktail Week, Tanqueray No. TEN has launched its ‘Make It a TEN’ residency at the renowned Artesian bar in The Langham Hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Night Sky Concert Lab is coming to St John&#39;s Smith Square</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-night-sky-concert-lab-is-coming-to-st-johns-smith-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-night-sky-concert-lab-is-coming-to-st-johns-smith-square/</guid>
      <description>The Night Sky Concert Lab is going to be at St John’s Smith Square this November for two performances – one at 7pm and one at 9pm. The show will feature music from the Southbank Sinfonia, conducted by Olivia Clarke, and will be narrated by NASA astronaut Mike Massimino, whilst images from the James Webb Telescope are displayed.&#xA;This event promises to be an immersive, sonic journey into the cosmos that has been sparking curiosity since the beginning of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in November 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</guid>
      <description>November in London marks the return of many beloved Christmas traditions across the city. Highlights include the switching on of Christmas lights and the return of festive ice skating at Somerset House. Music enthusiasts can enjoy celebrations for 30 years of Bugged Out! at Drumsheds, along with performances of Hansel and Gretel at the Royal Opera House. The art scene will be vibrant with the opening of several new exhibitions, including an exploration of photography in Britain during the 80s at Tate Britain, as well as the return of the Woolwich Contemporary Print Fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in October 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</guid>
      <description>October has arrived and London is back, and there are heaps of great events on. With Halloween events back in full swing, Black History Month and some of the best in arts and culture including Southbank’s London Literature Festival and Frieze London, it’s shaping up to be a big one!&#xA;Here are some of our favourite things you can do in the city this October.&#xA;Affordable Art Fair Battersea Autumn When: 20 – 23 October 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London this weekend: 8-10 March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this weekend: 8 –10 March 2024.&#xA;New York City Ballet (NYCB)&#xA;New York City Ballet, founded in 1948 by George Balanchine and Lincoln Kirstein, is renowned for its blend of contemporary creations and classic choreographies. Their upcoming performance in the UK presents a rare opportunity to witness the company&amp;rsquo;s world-class talent. The repertoire includes Justin Peck&amp;rsquo;s Rotunda, featuring a commissioned score by Nico Muhly, Duo Concertant by Balanchine, Pam Tanowitz&amp;rsquo;s Gustave le Gray No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOZI Restaurant Victoria Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</guid>
      <description>TOZI, derived from the affectionate Venetian slang for “a close-knit group of friends,” is the brainchild of an Italian trio that met while opening Shoreditch House under the Soho House Group. In 2013, Chef Maurilio Molteni, fresh from his time as Head Chef at Shoreditch House and developing the menu at Cecconi’s, opened the first TOZI restaurant in London. He was joined by Stefano Meloni and Marco Bullegas as restaurant manager and bar manager, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UVA: Synchronicity at 180 Studios Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/uva-synchronicity-at-180-studios-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/uva-synchronicity-at-180-studios-review/</guid>
      <description>In a city where immersive experiences have become a dime a dozen, with each vying for your hard-earned money, it&amp;rsquo;s no wonder that skepticism often prevails when new offerings hit your inbox. But let us assure you, Synchronicity by UVA at 180 Studios is not one of those exhibitions that leaves you questioning the value of your ticket.&#xA;Image: UVA: Synchronicity at 180 Studios. October 2023. © MTotoe.&#xA;Founded by Matt Clark in 2003, UVA (United Visual Artist) has earned international commissions from prestigious institutions, thanks to their unique blend of light, space, sound, and custom-made kinetic instruments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W London launches AMPLIFIED: a monthly live music series</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/w-london-launches-amplified-a-montly-live-music-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/w-london-launches-amplified-a-montly-live-music-series/</guid>
      <description>W London brings emerging local and international artists to Soho with exclusive performances at The Perception Bar.&#xA;W AMPLIFIED. Image credit Grant Walker.&#xA;This February, W London unveils AMPLIFIED, an electrifying monthly live music series at The Perception Bar, located inside the iconic hotel in the heart of Soho’s Leicester Square. Curated by DJ and W Music Curator Juss Jak (Jakki Degg), the series celebrates emerging talent from both local and international music scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 1 – 7 May 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-1-7-may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-1-7-may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 1 - 7 May 2023.&#xA;Explore London Unsound London&#xA;London&amp;rsquo;s groundbreaking Unsound event is returning after five years with three new works featuring innovative minds in electronic and experimental music. The boundary-pushing showcase includes performances by Osmium, a supergroup featuring Hildur Guðnadóttir, Sam Slater, James Ginzburg, and Rully Shabara of Senyawa. Custom-built instruments blend mechanical and organic sounds to create hypnotic music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 11 - 17 March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-11-17-march-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-11-17-march-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 11 – 17 March 2024.&#xA;Daunt Books Festival 2024&#xA;The Daunt Books two-day festival returns this week, featuring a series of talks at their quaint Marylebone store. It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect opportunity to gain insight into excellent reads. This year&amp;rsquo;s programme includes authors like Paul Lynch, Carys Davis, children&amp;rsquo;s book writer Lauren Child, and journalist Sathnam Sanghera. Events are individually ticketed. Click here for the line-up of events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 12 – 18 February 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-12-18-february-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-12-18-february-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 12 – 18 February 2024.&#xA;Guy Johnston and Britten Sinfonia: The Protecting Veil&#xA;Cellist Guy Johnston collaborates with Britten Sinfonia in a compelling concert featuring works by Tavener, Beethoven, and Bartók. Tavener&amp;rsquo;s The Protecting Veil showcases the cello&amp;rsquo;s emotive qualities, with Johnston&amp;rsquo;s performance reflecting his personal connection with the composer.&#xA;Date: 15 February 2024. Time: 7.30pm. Location: Barbican Centre, Silk Street, London</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 16  - 22 October 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-16-22-october-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-16-22-october-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 16 - 22 October 2023.&#xA;Bar takeovers for London Cocktail Week&#xA;London Cocktail Week is kicking off with some really exciting bar takeovers; bars from cities all of the world including Chicago, Barcelona, Toronto, India, and Copenhagen are taking over some of our favourite bars in the London. Launched in 2010, the 11-day festival celebrates London&amp;rsquo;s vibrant cocktail culture, and gives you the chance to try signature cocktails at numerous top bars across the city for just £8 - a steal in the current climate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 26 June – 2 July 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-26-june-2-july-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-26-june-2-july-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 26 June – 2 July 2023.&#xA;Explore London Chelsea &amp;amp; Kensington Festival 2023&#xA;Kensington and Chelsea Festival is returning for its third year this week. Taking place from 1 July - 31 August 2023. The festival will showcase a wide range of live art performances in various venues and outdoor spaces, featuring established artists and emerging talent. It offers a diverse cultural program including theatre, circus, opera, dance, music, outdoor arts, family shows, talks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s on in London this week: 23 – 29 September 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-23-29-september-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-23-29-september-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 23 – 29 September 2024.&#xA;Eugene Onegin&#xA;Experience the romantic drama of Tchaikovsky’s Eugene Onegin in a brand-new production by Ted Huffman. Making his Main Stage debut, Huffman explores themes of memory and desire through this classic tale. Featuring Gordon Bintner as Onegin and Kristina Mkhitaryan as Tatyana, with Henrik Nánási conducting, this production offers a fresh perspective on a timeless story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s on in London this week: 3 - 9 February 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-3-9-february-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-3-9-february-2025/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 3 - 9 February 2025.&#xA;Orchid Festival&#xA;Kew Gardens’ annual Orchid Festival has returned, celebrating Peru’s vibrant flora and fauna. The Princess of Wales Conservatory features orchids, alpacas, flamingos, and large-scale photography by Peruvian artist Mariano Vivanco, as well as murals by Lima-born Gisella Stapleton.&#xA;Date: 1 February - 2 March 2025. Location: Princess of Wales Conservatory Kew, Richmond, London, TW9 3AE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to find London&#39;s best ice cream parlours this summer 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>London’s summer weather may be unpredictable, but its ice cream parlours are always ready for sunny days. From the return of Anya Hindmarch’s Ice Cream Project to delicious soft serve in Chinatown and neighbourhood favourite Udderlicious, here are some of our top spots to enjoy ice cream in London this summer.&#xA;The Ice Cream Project III Anya Hindmarch ice cream project III. Photo by MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Returning for its third year, The Ice Cream Project is back at The Village from 7 June to 18 August, offering unexpectedly delicious ice creams and sorbets inspired by Anya Hindmarch&amp;rsquo;s favourite cult food brands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your guide to Marylebone Village Christmas Lights switch-on</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/marylebone-village-christmas-lights-switch-on-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/marylebone-village-christmas-lights-switch-on-2024/</guid>
      <description>Marylebone Village Christmas festivities return on 13 November with live performances, artisan markets, festive activities, and the magical lights switch-on.&#xA;Marylebone Village Christmas festivities return on 13 November 2024.&#xA;Marylebone Village is set to kick off the festive season with its annual Christmas lights switch-on event, taking place on Wednesday 13 November 2024. From 3–8pm, visitors can enjoy a magical evening of festive activities, an artisan market, live music, and late-night shopping.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
