<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London11 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london11/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London11 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london11/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hiroshi Sugimoto: Time Machine at The Hayward Gallery review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hiroshi-sugimoto-time-machine-at-the-hayward-gallery-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hiroshi-sugimoto-time-machine-at-the-hayward-gallery-review/</guid>
      <description>Hiroshi Sugimoto’s awe-inspiring photographs are currently on display at the Hayward Gallery. It is the largest survey to date of this artist in the UK and it is spellbinding, some rooms much more than others. For over 50 years, Sugimoto has been creating multiple extraordinary, enigmatic photographic series playing with light and dark, life and death, and these are all now on display for us to admire and question what is truth and what is not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford Street Christmas lights to return in November</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</guid>
      <description>Oxford Street&amp;rsquo;s dazzling Christmas lights are poised to make a grand return on 2 November, ushering in the festive spirit throughout London.&#xA;Image: Oxford Street Christmas lights to return 2 November 2023.&#xA;On 2 November, the festive season will kick off on Oxford Street as its renowned Christmas lights illuminate the iconic London street. The city&amp;rsquo;s ultimate holiday destination will shine brightly with brilliant white stars (and lots of people capturing Instagram-worthy pictures), creating that magical Christmas atmosphere we associate with London during this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UVA: Synchronicity at 180 Studios Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/uva-synchronicity-at-180-studios-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/uva-synchronicity-at-180-studios-review/</guid>
      <description>In a city where immersive experiences have become a dime a dozen, with each vying for your hard-earned money, it&amp;rsquo;s no wonder that skepticism often prevails when new offerings hit your inbox. But let us assure you, Synchronicity by UVA at 180 Studios is not one of those exhibitions that leaves you questioning the value of your ticket.&#xA;Image: UVA: Synchronicity at 180 Studios. October 2023. © MTotoe.&#xA;Founded by Matt Clark in 2003, UVA (United Visual Artist) has earned international commissions from prestigious institutions, thanks to their unique blend of light, space, sound, and custom-made kinetic instruments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 16  - 22 October 2023</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-16-22-october-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-16-22-october-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 16 - 22 October 2023.&#xA;Bar takeovers for London Cocktail Week&#xA;London Cocktail Week is kicking off with some really exciting bar takeovers; bars from cities all of the world including Chicago, Barcelona, Toronto, India, and Copenhagen are taking over some of our favourite bars in the London. Launched in 2010, the 11-day festival celebrates London&amp;rsquo;s vibrant cocktail culture, and gives you the chance to try signature cocktails at numerous top bars across the city for just £8 - a steal in the current climate.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
