<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artnews on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/artnews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artnews on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/artnews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A  new exhibition exploring the work of the Renaissance master Donatello is coming to the V&amp;A</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-new-exhibition-exploring-the-work-of-the-renaissance-master-donatello-is-coming-to-the-vampa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-new-exhibition-exploring-the-work-of-the-renaissance-master-donatello-is-coming-to-the-vampa/</guid>
      <description>Victoria &amp;amp; Albert Museum to stage first major UK exhibition to explore the work of the Renaissance master Donatello, including artworks never seen before in the UK.&#xA;Image: San Rossore, Donatello, by permission of the Ministry of Culture – Regional Directorate of Museums of Tuscany, Florence, Italy&#xA;Opening February 2023, Donatello: Sculpting the Renaissance will be the first major UK exhibition to explore the exceptional talents of the Renaissance master, Donatello.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An exhibition exploring art and culture of Spain and the Hispanic world will be coming to the Royal Academy of Arts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/an-exhibition-exploring-art-and-culture-of-spain-and-the-hispanic-world-will-be-coming-to-the-royal-academy-of-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/an-exhibition-exploring-art-and-culture-of-spain-and-the-hispanic-world-will-be-coming-to-the-royal-academy-of-arts/</guid>
      <description>The Royal Academy of Arts will present Spain and the Hispanic World, showcasing masterpieces by Goya and Velázquez to objects from Latin America.&#xA;Image: Joaquín Sorolla,Vision of Spain (sketch) (detail), 1912-1913. Gouache on kraft paper. 107 x 191 cm. On loan from The Hispanic Society of America, New York, NY.&#xA;In January 2023, the Royal Academy of Arts will present Spain and the Hispanic World, celebrating the unrivalled collection of the Hispanic Society Museum &amp;amp; Library in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mediterranean will be at the heart of ARCOmadrid 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-mediterranean-will-be-at-the-heart-of-arcomadrid-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-mediterranean-will-be-at-the-heart-of-arcomadrid-2023/</guid>
      <description>The 42nd edition of ARCOmadrid, the fair organised by IFEMA MADRID, will be held from 22 -26 February 2023 with the Mediterranean as its core project.&#xA;Image: courtesy of ARCOmadrid&#xA;ARCOmadrid 2023 curated by Marina Fokidis with the advice of Bouchra Khalili and Hila Peleg will revolve around the art scenes of the countries surrounding it, from south to north and coast to coast. The curatorial team will present a series of artists and galleries from the countries of this rich and complex geography.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
