<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London6 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london6/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London6 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best restaurants to eat light and wholesome food in London</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Discover London&amp;rsquo;s top destinations for light, nutritious, and wholesome food with our guide. From the ever-popular vegetarian favourite KIN Cafe to the renowned Maggie Jones&amp;rsquo;s, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a range of options to satisfy your cravings.&#xA;Image: Dan Gold&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a dining experience in London that is both delicious and nutritious, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. Our six restaurant recommendations offer a delightful selection of light, flavourful meals that are not only wholesome but also leave you feeling energised and fully satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakin’ Convention 2023 review - International Festival of Hip Hop Dance Theatre</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/breakin-convention-2023-review-international-festival-of-hip-hop-dance-theatre-exwpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/breakin-convention-2023-review-international-festival-of-hip-hop-dance-theatre-exwpm/</guid>
      <description>An evening of inspiring performances from local and global talent at Sadler&amp;rsquo;s Wells, as Breakin&amp;rsquo; Convention celebrates its 20th anniversary.&#xA;Image: Credit Belinda Lawley - Breakin&amp;rsquo; Convention 2023 - Boy Blue (6).JPG&#xA;We had the pleasure of attending the 20th-anniversary celebration of the renowned international hip-hop dance festival, Breakin&amp;rsquo; Convention, at Sadler&amp;rsquo;s Wells on Saturday evening. The show began with Jonzi D, the festival&amp;rsquo;s founder, taking the stage to reflect on the event&amp;rsquo;s history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printworks London closure: the venue whose spirit lives on</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/printworks-closure-the-venue-whose-spirit-lives-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/printworks-closure-the-venue-whose-spirit-lives-on/</guid>
      <description>The closure of Printworks marks the end of an era for London&amp;rsquo;s clubbing scene, but the legacy of this iconic venue will undoubtedly live on.&#xA;Image: Closing weekend at Printworks London. © Emma Chadwick&#xA;It was a sad weekend for London’s ravers as the iconic Printworks nightclub closed its doors for the last time. Artists including Peggy Gou, Sub Focus and Black Coffee gathered in the press halls for a final send-off, creating the fantastic atmosphere and energy that the venue is known and loved for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOLAIRE CULTURE, An Exhibition Celebrating 250 Years of Veuve Clicquot will open in London in May 2023</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/solaire-culture-an-exhibition-celebrating-250-years-of-veuve-clicquot-will-open-in-london-in-may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/solaire-culture-an-exhibition-celebrating-250-years-of-veuve-clicquot-will-open-in-london-in-may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Veuve Clicquot announces today the next chapter of the highly successful global exhibition, SOLAIRE CULTURE, to celebrate 250 years of the iconic house. After debuting in Tokyo and Los Angeles in 2022, the exhibition is travelling to London, to take over Piccadilly Circus in May 2023.&#xA;Image: Veuve Clicquot “Solaire Culture” exhibition, Yayoi Kusama, Tokyo, 2022&#xA;SOLAIRE CULTURE celebrates Veuve Clicquot&amp;rsquo;s 250 years of history, focusing on the legacy of Madame Clicquot, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s first female entrepreneurs who took over the reins of the house in 1805, and the contemporary vision of the curator, Camille Morineau, and designer Constance Guisset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 1 – 7 May 2023</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-1-7-may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-1-7-may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 1 - 7 May 2023.&#xA;Explore London Unsound London&#xA;London&amp;rsquo;s groundbreaking Unsound event is returning after five years with three new works featuring innovative minds in electronic and experimental music. The boundary-pushing showcase includes performances by Osmium, a supergroup featuring Hildur Guðnadóttir, Sam Slater, James Ginzburg, and Rully Shabara of Senyawa. Custom-built instruments blend mechanical and organic sounds to create hypnotic music.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
