<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food5 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/food5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food5 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/food5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Highroad Social: Greenwich’s newest restaurant has hit the dining scene</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/highroad-social-greenwich-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/highroad-social-greenwich-review/</guid>
      <description>On a sunny Friday we decided to make a day of it and journey to Greenwich from West London. We set off from Putney Pier via Uber Boat for the 90-minute trip to Greenwich to be tourists for the day in our beloved city. It is rather wonderful seeing the city from the water going under iconic bridges such as Albert Bridge, Westminster Bridge, Millennium Bridge and Tower Bridge and passing some iconic London Landmarks; Battersea Power Station, Houses of Parliament, Big Ben, the Millennium Wheel, The Shard, Tate Modern, Tower of London and the stunning modern skyline of the Square Mile and eventually all the old shipping wharfs as we neared our destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanqueray No. TEN launches ‘Make It a TEN’ Residency at Artesian</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tanqueray-no-ten-launches-make-it-a-ten-residency-at-artesian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tanqueray-no-ten-launches-make-it-a-ten-residency-at-artesian/</guid>
      <description>Stanley Tucci and head bartender Giulia Cuccurullo present a curated cocktail experience at Artesian, located in The Langham Hotel, in celebration of London Cocktail Week.&#xA;Stanley Tucci and head bartender Giulia Cuccurullo present a curated cocktail experience at Artesian, in celebration of London Cocktail Week from 3 - 31 October 2024.&#xA;In celebration of London Cocktail Week, Tanqueray No. TEN has launched its ‘Make It a TEN’ residency at the renowned Artesian bar in The Langham Hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOZI Restaurant Victoria Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</guid>
      <description>TOZI, derived from the affectionate Venetian slang for “a close-knit group of friends,” is the brainchild of an Italian trio that met while opening Shoreditch House under the Soho House Group. In 2013, Chef Maurilio Molteni, fresh from his time as Head Chef at Shoreditch House and developing the menu at Cecconi’s, opened the first TOZI restaurant in London. He was joined by Stefano Meloni and Marco Bullegas as restaurant manager and bar manager, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to find London&#39;s best ice cream parlours this summer 2024</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/where-to-find-londons-best-ice-cream-parlours-this-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>London’s summer weather may be unpredictable, but its ice cream parlours are always ready for sunny days. From the return of Anya Hindmarch’s Ice Cream Project to delicious soft serve in Chinatown and neighbourhood favourite Udderlicious, here are some of our top spots to enjoy ice cream in London this summer.&#xA;The Ice Cream Project III Anya Hindmarch ice cream project III. Photo by MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Returning for its third year, The Ice Cream Project is back at The Village from 7 June to 18 August, offering unexpectedly delicious ice creams and sorbets inspired by Anya Hindmarch&amp;rsquo;s favourite cult food brands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
