<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thescene2 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/thescene2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thescene2 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/thescene2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breakin’ Convention 2023 review - International Festival of Hip Hop Dance Theatre</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/breakin-convention-2023-review-international-festival-of-hip-hop-dance-theatre-exwpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/breakin-convention-2023-review-international-festival-of-hip-hop-dance-theatre-exwpm/</guid>
      <description>An evening of inspiring performances from local and global talent at Sadler&amp;rsquo;s Wells, as Breakin&amp;rsquo; Convention celebrates its 20th anniversary.&#xA;Image: Credit Belinda Lawley - Breakin&amp;rsquo; Convention 2023 - Boy Blue (6).JPG&#xA;We had the pleasure of attending the 20th-anniversary celebration of the renowned international hip-hop dance festival, Breakin&amp;rsquo; Convention, at Sadler&amp;rsquo;s Wells on Saturday evening. The show began with Jonzi D, the festival&amp;rsquo;s founder, taking the stage to reflect on the event&amp;rsquo;s history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitality In The Woods festival 2023 review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-festival-2023-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-festival-2023-review/</guid>
      <description>Hospitality in the Woods festival makes a triumphant return to London.&#xA;Image: Hospitality In The Woods 2023. Beckhenham Palace Park. © Trade Photographer.&#xA;Leaving the tram at Beckenham Junction, you’d have been hard pressed to believe there was anything significant going on in the town on Saturday as dog walkers and brunchers milled about, basking in the glorious summer weather. However, just a short walk away, Beckenham Place Park welcomed a sea of bucket hats and became home to one of the most recognisable festival in Drum &amp;amp; Bass for the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printworks London closure: the venue whose spirit lives on</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/printworks-closure-the-venue-whose-spirit-lives-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/printworks-closure-the-venue-whose-spirit-lives-on/</guid>
      <description>The closure of Printworks marks the end of an era for London&amp;rsquo;s clubbing scene, but the legacy of this iconic venue will undoubtedly live on.&#xA;Image: Closing weekend at Printworks London. © Emma Chadwick&#xA;It was a sad weekend for London’s ravers as the iconic Printworks nightclub closed its doors for the last time. Artists including Peggy Gou, Sub Focus and Black Coffee gathered in the press halls for a final send-off, creating the fantastic atmosphere and energy that the venue is known and loved for.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
