<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Icw4 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/icw4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Icw4 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/icw4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Nimrod Vardi and Claudel Goy, directors of arebyte gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nimrod-vardi-and-claudel-goy-the-directors-of-arebyte-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nimrod-vardi-and-claudel-goy-the-directors-of-arebyte-gallery/</guid>
      <description>“To us, immersive doesn’t just mean 360° projections or putting on a VR headset. It means telling a story that invites people in, that shifts their perception, and brings them along for the journey.”&#xA;- Nimrod Vardi&#xA;Nimrod Vardi and Claudel Goy, the Directors of arebyte gallery&#xA;Venturing outside the usual Central London art stomping grounds can sometimes feel like an effort. But often, it is really worth it. Case in point for arebyte Gallery, currently based on London City Island (but moving all their programming to Camden soon).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Elisabeth Mulenga</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-elisabeth-mulenga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-elisabeth-mulenga/</guid>
      <description>“As a performer, a lot of my inspiration comes from a desire to experience different versions of myself, access different identities…”&#xA;- Elisabeth Mulenga&#xA;Image: Elisabeth Mulenga. © Jack Thomson.&#xA;Elisabeth Mulenga is a dance artist whose work is at once unflinching, tender, and intimate, and takes inspiration from film directors to explore the human psyche. Mulenga is an alumnus of the eighth cohort of National Youth Dance Company (NYDC) and won the Choreographic Innovation Award in the final of BBC Young Dancer 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Varvara Roza</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-varvara-roza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-varvara-roza/</guid>
      <description>“…I am genuinely committed to the promotion of artists whose work is utterly integral to the landscape of contemporary art, because art, to me, is so much more than an asset class&amp;hellip;”&#xA;- Varvara Roza&#xA;Varvara Roza.&#xA;Working from core values of trust and commitment, Varvara Roza is an increasingly renowned private art advisor and artist representative on the London scene whose verve and passion for bringing leading contemporary artists to the global stage is second to none.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
