<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Explore London on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/explore-london/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Explore London on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/explore-london/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in June in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>June in London is buzzing with excitement as festival season kicks off and some much-loved events return. From Southbank Centre&amp;rsquo;s Meltdown festival, curated by the legendary Chaka Khan, to the delightful lunchtime Jazz Series at Cadogan Hall. Add in the Sundance Film Festival and the revival of Open Water Swimming, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got a month packed with fantastic activities. Here&amp;rsquo;s our selection of things to do in London this June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London’s best indoor green spaces to escape the winter blues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</guid>
      <description>When the winter chill sets in and the London skies are often grey and rainy, indoor green spaces offer the perfect escape. From towering tropical plants to lush Victorian conservatories, here are some of the most remarkable indoor gardens to visit in London, providing a serene environment for relaxation and inspiration, no matter the weather.&#xA;Barbican Conservatory Barbican Conservatory, Barbican Centre. © MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Step into a hidden world of exotic plants and trees at the Barbican Conservatory, a tropical oasis nestled within the iconic Barbican Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in November 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</guid>
      <description>November in London marks the return of many beloved Christmas traditions across the city. Highlights include the switching on of Christmas lights and the return of festive ice skating at Somerset House. Music enthusiasts can enjoy celebrations for 30 years of Bugged Out! at Drumsheds, along with performances of Hansel and Gretel at the Royal Opera House. The art scene will be vibrant with the opening of several new exhibitions, including an exploration of photography in Britain during the 80s at Tate Britain, as well as the return of the Woolwich Contemporary Print Fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in October 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</guid>
      <description>October has arrived and London is back, and there are heaps of great events on. With Halloween events back in full swing, Black History Month and some of the best in arts and culture including Southbank’s London Literature Festival and Frieze London, it’s shaping up to be a big one!&#xA;Here are some of our favourite things you can do in the city this October.&#xA;Affordable Art Fair Battersea Autumn When: 20 – 23 October 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London this weekend: 8-10 March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this weekend: 8 –10 March 2024.&#xA;New York City Ballet (NYCB)&#xA;New York City Ballet, founded in 1948 by George Balanchine and Lincoln Kirstein, is renowned for its blend of contemporary creations and classic choreographies. Their upcoming performance in the UK presents a rare opportunity to witness the company&amp;rsquo;s world-class talent. The repertoire includes Justin Peck&amp;rsquo;s Rotunda, featuring a commissioned score by Nico Muhly, Duo Concertant by Balanchine, Pam Tanowitz&amp;rsquo;s Gustave le Gray No.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
