<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Explore London on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/explore-london/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Explore London on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/explore-london/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in June in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-june-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>June in London is buzzing with excitement as festival season kicks off and some much-loved events return. From Southbank Centre&amp;rsquo;s Meltdown festival, curated by the legendary Chaka Khan, to the delightful lunchtime Jazz Series at Cadogan Hall. Add in the Sundance Film Festival and the revival of Open Water Swimming, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got a month packed with fantastic activities. Here&amp;rsquo;s our selection of things to do in London this June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: best walks in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourites-best-walks-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourites-best-walks-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Walks have been very in vogue over the last few months, and London really does have a whole host of amazing locations for a wander. From an art-filled strolls, to walks along the Thames, here are some of our favourite places to walk around in the city.&#xA;The Line Image: Alex Chinneck&#xA;The Line is a 7.7km route from Queen Elizabeth Olympic Park to the O2 that follows the line of Greenwich Meridian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: things to do this weekend in London (14th - 16th February 2020)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/p8na0iut7nq41ap9e60i2yd64m7u53/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/p8na0iut7nq41ap9e60i2yd64m7u53/</guid>
      <description>For the arty ones… Steve McQueen at Tate Steve McQueen exhibition at Tate Modern When?&#xA;13th February – 11th May 2020&#xA;Price: £13&#xA;#FLODown: Tate Modern presents the first major exhibition of Turner Prize-winning artist and Oscar-winning filmmaker Steve McQueen. The exhibition features 14 major works spanning across film, photography and sculpture. The exhibition includes his first film that was shot on a Super 8 camera, Exodus 1992/97, and the more recent End Credits2012–on-going.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A guide to the most beautiful historic houses to visit in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-guide-to-the-most-beautiful-historic-homes-to-visit-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-guide-to-the-most-beautiful-historic-homes-to-visit-in-london/</guid>
      <description>London boasts an array of remarkable historic homes, each offering a unique glimpse into different eras. From classic Tudor dwellings to elegant Georgian townhouses and residences that provide insights into the Victorian era, there&amp;rsquo;s a diverse selection to explore. Whether you adore exquisite interiors or are intrigued by history and artistic masterpieces, here is our guide to beautiful historic houses to visit in London.&#xA;Sir John Soane&amp;rsquo;s Museum Sir John Soane&amp;rsquo;s Museum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best green spaces to visit in London in summer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-green-spaces-to-visit-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-green-spaces-to-visit-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Among our passions for art and exploring bakeries, we also cherish London&amp;rsquo;s green spaces. From vast areas like the Walthamstow Wetlands to hidden gems like Phoenix Gardens and Mount Street Gardens, there&amp;rsquo;s a wealth of tranquil spots waiting to be explored. Here are our top choices of green spaces to fully embrace London&amp;rsquo;s summer in 2024.&#xA;Phoenix Garden Phoenix Garden, St Giles. Photo by MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Tucked away behind the Phoenix Theatre in St Giles, the Phoenix Garden offers a peaceful haven in the midst of busy Soho and Covent Garden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best markets in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-markets-in-londonrqmarket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-markets-in-londonrqmarket/</guid>
      <description>The London market is at the epicentre of London life from the avid foodie to the antique collector and fashionistas alike, we all want in on the market scene. There is nothing like a Sunday afternoon trip to the market, here is our guide to the best markets in London.&#xA;Columbia Road Flower Market Columbia Road Flower Market situated in trendy Shoreditch is home to several flower stalls. You’ll find friendly traders selling buckets full of the finest cut flowers, bulbs, herbs and garden fittings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best parks in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-parks-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-parks-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Escaping the hectic streets of London is a necessity for many of us, whether its getting lost in a book, going for a walk, or enjoying a picnic with friends there are several activities on offer in London’s many parks. Here’s our guide to the best London parks and all you need to know when you get there.&#xA;Hyde Park Hyde Park is 350 acres of beauty located in the heart of the city, complete with beautiful man-made serpentine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover exceptional jazz at Ladbroke Hall this April</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-month-of-exceptional-jazz-at-ladbroke-hall-this-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-month-of-exceptional-jazz-at-ladbroke-hall-this-april/</guid>
      <description>This April, Ladbroke Hall’s renowned Friday Jazz &amp;amp; Dinner series returns, showcasing an impressive roster of artists at its Sunbeam Theatre. Each evening pairs exceptional live jazz with a carefully crafted menu from the award-winning Pollini restaurant. With tickets priced at £15 for standing and £30 for table seating, the series offers an intimate setting to enjoy world-class music in the heart of West London.&#xA;© Ladbroke Hall&#xA;The month opens on 4 April with saxophonist Alex Garnett, who will be joined by Will Barry (piano), Ferg Ireland (double bass), and Will Cleasby (drums).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitality in the Woods returns to London in August 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-returns-to-london-nbspin-august-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hospitality-in-the-woods-returns-to-london-nbspin-august-2023/</guid>
      <description>Hospitality in the Woods makes its comeback to the picturesque Beckenham Place Park in August 2023, featuring a jam-packed lineup of Drum &amp;amp; Bass stars.&#xA;Image: Hospitality In The Woods.&#xA;Get ready for the return of Hospitality In The Woods, a legendary showcase of Drum &amp;amp; Bass excellence set to take place on 19 August at Beckenham Place Park. Headlined by Netsky and High Contrast, this electrifying festival will feature five curated stages of non-stop, banging music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London’s best indoor green spaces to escape the winter blues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/londons-best-indoor-green-spaces-to-escape-the-winter-blues/</guid>
      <description>When the winter chill sets in and the London skies are often grey and rainy, indoor green spaces offer the perfect escape. From towering tropical plants to lush Victorian conservatories, here are some of the most remarkable indoor gardens to visit in London, providing a serene environment for relaxation and inspiration, no matter the weather.&#xA;Barbican Conservatory Barbican Conservatory, Barbican Centre. © MTotoe.&#xA;#FLODown: Step into a hidden world of exotic plants and trees at the Barbican Conservatory, a tropical oasis nestled within the iconic Barbican Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford Street Christmas lights to return in November</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/oxford-street-christmas-lights-to-return-in-november/</guid>
      <description>Oxford Street&amp;rsquo;s dazzling Christmas lights are poised to make a grand return on 2 November, ushering in the festive spirit throughout London.&#xA;Image: Oxford Street Christmas lights to return 2 November 2023.&#xA;On 2 November, the festive season will kick off on Oxford Street as its renowned Christmas lights illuminate the iconic London street. The city&amp;rsquo;s ultimate holiday destination will shine brightly with brilliant white stars (and lots of people capturing Instagram-worthy pictures), creating that magical Christmas atmosphere we associate with London during this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pauline Loctin&#39;s ‘Flying in Nuanced Colours’ to debut at Uncommon Holborn for London Design Festival 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pauline-loctin-installation-to-debut-at-uncommon-holborn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pauline-loctin-installation-to-debut-at-uncommon-holborn/</guid>
      <description>Uncommon Holborn to present Pauline Loctin’s ‘Flying in Nuanced Colours’— a major paper sculpture installation for London Design Festival in September.&#xA;Pauline Loctin x Uncommon Holborn. Photo by Mark Cocksedge.&#xA;This September, Uncommon Holborn will host Flying in Nuanced Colours, a striking installation by renowned paper sculptor Pauline Loctin, as part of London Design Festival 2024. The exhibition, a bespoke commission for the B Corp certified workspace provider, merges traditional origami with modern art to create a captivating visual experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanqueray No. TEN launches ‘Make It a TEN’ Residency at Artesian</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tanqueray-no-ten-launches-make-it-a-ten-residency-at-artesian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tanqueray-no-ten-launches-make-it-a-ten-residency-at-artesian/</guid>
      <description>Stanley Tucci and head bartender Giulia Cuccurullo present a curated cocktail experience at Artesian, located in The Langham Hotel, in celebration of London Cocktail Week.&#xA;Stanley Tucci and head bartender Giulia Cuccurullo present a curated cocktail experience at Artesian, in celebration of London Cocktail Week from 3 - 31 October 2024.&#xA;In celebration of London Cocktail Week, Tanqueray No. TEN has launched its ‘Make It a TEN’ residency at the renowned Artesian bar in The Langham Hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The European art exhibitions worth travelling for in autumn 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-european-art-exhibitions-worth-travelling-for-in-autumn-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-european-art-exhibitions-worth-travelling-for-in-autumn-2024/</guid>
      <description>With several art fairs and art weeks scheduled across Europe this autumn, there are numerous reasons to travel. From delving into Berlin&amp;rsquo;s dynamic 90s scene to attending the Frans Hals exhibition in the same city, and exploring a group exhibition focused on textile storytelling in Amsterdam, there’s much to anticipate. This is your essential guide to the must-see art exhibitions in Paris, Berlin, and Amsterdam this autumn, along with our top recommendations for the pavilions at the 2024 Venice Biennale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Night Sky Concert Lab is coming to St John&#39;s Smith Square</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-night-sky-concert-lab-is-coming-to-st-johns-smith-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-night-sky-concert-lab-is-coming-to-st-johns-smith-square/</guid>
      <description>The Night Sky Concert Lab is going to be at St John’s Smith Square this November for two performances – one at 7pm and one at 9pm. The show will feature music from the Southbank Sinfonia, conducted by Olivia Clarke, and will be narrated by NASA astronaut Mike Massimino, whilst images from the James Webb Telescope are displayed.&#xA;This event promises to be an immersive, sonic journey into the cosmos that has been sparking curiosity since the beginning of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in November 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-november-2024/</guid>
      <description>November in London marks the return of many beloved Christmas traditions across the city. Highlights include the switching on of Christmas lights and the return of festive ice skating at Somerset House. Music enthusiasts can enjoy celebrations for 30 years of Bugged Out! at Drumsheds, along with performances of Hansel and Gretel at the Royal Opera House. The art scene will be vibrant with the opening of several new exhibitions, including an exploration of photography in Britain during the 80s at Tate Britain, as well as the return of the Woolwich Contemporary Print Fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London in October 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-in-october-2022/</guid>
      <description>October has arrived and London is back, and there are heaps of great events on. With Halloween events back in full swing, Black History Month and some of the best in arts and culture including Southbank’s London Literature Festival and Frieze London, it’s shaping up to be a big one!&#xA;Here are some of our favourite things you can do in the city this October.&#xA;Affordable Art Fair Battersea Autumn When: 20 – 23 October 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in London this weekend: 8-10 March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/things-to-do-in-london-this-weekend-8-10-march-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this weekend: 8 –10 March 2024.&#xA;New York City Ballet (NYCB)&#xA;New York City Ballet, founded in 1948 by George Balanchine and Lincoln Kirstein, is renowned for its blend of contemporary creations and classic choreographies. Their upcoming performance in the UK presents a rare opportunity to witness the company&amp;rsquo;s world-class talent. The repertoire includes Justin Peck&amp;rsquo;s Rotunda, featuring a commissioned score by Nico Muhly, Duo Concertant by Balanchine, Pam Tanowitz&amp;rsquo;s Gustave le Gray No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 1 – 7 May 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-1-7-may-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-1-7-may-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 1 - 7 May 2023.&#xA;Explore London Unsound London&#xA;London&amp;rsquo;s groundbreaking Unsound event is returning after five years with three new works featuring innovative minds in electronic and experimental music. The boundary-pushing showcase includes performances by Osmium, a supergroup featuring Hildur Guðnadóttir, Sam Slater, James Ginzburg, and Rully Shabara of Senyawa. Custom-built instruments blend mechanical and organic sounds to create hypnotic music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 11 - 17 March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-11-17-march-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-11-17-march-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 11 – 17 March 2024.&#xA;Daunt Books Festival 2024&#xA;The Daunt Books two-day festival returns this week, featuring a series of talks at their quaint Marylebone store. It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect opportunity to gain insight into excellent reads. This year&amp;rsquo;s programme includes authors like Paul Lynch, Carys Davis, children&amp;rsquo;s book writer Lauren Child, and journalist Sathnam Sanghera. Events are individually ticketed. Click here for the line-up of events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 12 – 18 February 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-12-18-february-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-12-18-february-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 12 – 18 February 2024.&#xA;Guy Johnston and Britten Sinfonia: The Protecting Veil&#xA;Cellist Guy Johnston collaborates with Britten Sinfonia in a compelling concert featuring works by Tavener, Beethoven, and Bartók. Tavener&amp;rsquo;s The Protecting Veil showcases the cello&amp;rsquo;s emotive qualities, with Johnston&amp;rsquo;s performance reflecting his personal connection with the composer.&#xA;Date: 15 February 2024. Time: 7.30pm. Location: Barbican Centre, Silk Street, London</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 16  - 22 October 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-16-22-october-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-16-22-october-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 16 - 22 October 2023.&#xA;Bar takeovers for London Cocktail Week&#xA;London Cocktail Week is kicking off with some really exciting bar takeovers; bars from cities all of the world including Chicago, Barcelona, Toronto, India, and Copenhagen are taking over some of our favourite bars in the London. Launched in 2010, the 11-day festival celebrates London&amp;rsquo;s vibrant cocktail culture, and gives you the chance to try signature cocktails at numerous top bars across the city for just £8 - a steal in the current climate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 26 June – 2 July 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-26-june-2-july-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-26-june-2-july-2023/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of things to do in London this week: 26 June – 2 July 2023.&#xA;Explore London Chelsea &amp;amp; Kensington Festival 2023&#xA;Kensington and Chelsea Festival is returning for its third year this week. Taking place from 1 July - 31 August 2023. The festival will showcase a wide range of live art performances in various venues and outdoor spaces, featuring established artists and emerging talent. It offers a diverse cultural program including theatre, circus, opera, dance, music, outdoor arts, family shows, talks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s on in London this week: 23 – 29 September 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-23-29-september-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-23-29-september-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 23 – 29 September 2024.&#xA;Eugene Onegin&#xA;Experience the romantic drama of Tchaikovsky’s Eugene Onegin in a brand-new production by Ted Huffman. Making his Main Stage debut, Huffman explores themes of memory and desire through this classic tale. Featuring Gordon Bintner as Onegin and Kristina Mkhitaryan as Tatyana, with Henrik Nánási conducting, this production offers a fresh perspective on a timeless story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s on in London this week: 3 - 9 February 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-3-9-february-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-3-9-february-2025/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 3 - 9 February 2025.&#xA;Orchid Festival&#xA;Kew Gardens’ annual Orchid Festival has returned, celebrating Peru’s vibrant flora and fauna. The Princess of Wales Conservatory features orchids, alpacas, flamingos, and large-scale photography by Peruvian artist Mariano Vivanco, as well as murals by Lima-born Gisella Stapleton.&#xA;Date: 1 February - 2 March 2025. Location: Princess of Wales Conservatory Kew, Richmond, London, TW9 3AE.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
