<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FLO Drink on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/categories/flo-drink/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FLO Drink on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/categories/flo-drink/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#FLODown: Barts</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-barts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-barts/</guid>
      <description>Photos: Barts&#xA;Barts is a speakeasy styled cocktail bar on Sloane Avenue. Dimly-lit and filled with quirky ornaments, their menu is inspired by comic books and features a number of unique and creative cocktails. From the ‘Mad Hatter’ served in a top hat, to the ‘Chelsea Rose’ is served in quaint little tea cups by friendly barman dressed like ‘cheeky chappies’ straight out of Oliver Twist with newsboy caps. With their incredible cocktail selection and live music, there is a lot of fun to be had at Barts!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLODown: Boundary Shoreditch</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-boundary-shoreditch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-boundary-shoreditch/</guid>
      <description>Boundary is perched on top of a boutique hotel in the heart of Shoreditch, and it offers panoramic views of Shoreditch. The rooftop features gorgeous citrus trees and an outdoor terrace complete with an open-wood-fire and cosy furnishing that will make you feel right at home. The rooftop is opened all year round with a menu that changes according to the season. Boundary is equipped to deal with the change in weather, and they provide heaters and blankets to keep you toasty in the winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: The Nest Rooftop Bar</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flofavourite-the-nest-rooftop-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flofavourite-the-nest-rooftop-bar/</guid>
      <description>Image: MTotoe&#xA;The Nest is a welcome addition to London’s plethora of rooftop bars and is located just a short walk from Oxford Circus station. The bar sits on the 16th floor of the Treehouse Hotel which opened just under a year ago. It’s a quirky, green haven filled with wooden furniture and a wraparound terrace, offering 360-degree views of the city.&#xA;Whilst the food menu isn&amp;rsquo;t particularly extensive, think small plates and light snacks, they do have a great selection of cocktails to make up for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best bars for a date night in London</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-bars-for-a-date-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-bars-for-a-date-night/</guid>
      <description>Planning a date night is stressful enough as it is, so we’re here to ease some of that stress by giving you some best bars in London for a date night. Whether you’re after a romantic setting to impress your Bumble date (who you‘ve been getting to know virtually over the last couple of months) or a cool location to excite your partner, we’ve got you covered.&#xA;IRIS Bar at the Gherkin Image: The Gherkin</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
