<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artnews6 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/artnews6/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artnews6 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/artnews6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lindokuhle Sobekwa wins 2025 Deutsche Börse Photography Foundation Prize</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/lindokuhle-sobekwa-wins-2025-deutsche-brse-photography-foundation-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/lindokuhle-sobekwa-wins-2025-deutsche-brse-photography-foundation-prize/</guid>
      <description>Lindokuhle Sobekwa honoured for powerful tribute to his late sister and a poignant reflection on South Africa’s social history.&#xA;Lindokuhle Sobekwa. The Photographers’ Gallery. Deutsche Börse Photography Foundation Prize 2025. Image credit Heather Shuker.&#xA;South African photographer Lindokuhle Sobekwa has been awarded the 2025 Deutsche Börse Photography Foundation Prize for his personal photobook I carry Her photo with Me. The £30,000 prize, announced on 15 May at The Photographers’ Gallery in London by author and photographer Caleb Azumah Nelson, celebrates the most significant contribution to international contemporary photography over the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southbank Centre’s new Festival “Multitudes” to open in April 2025</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/southbank-centres-new-festival-multitudes-to-open-in-april-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/southbank-centres-new-festival-multitudes-to-open-in-april-2025/</guid>
      <description>Multitudes at Southbank Centre will reimagine live music through bold collaborations across dance, theatre, and visual arts.&#xA;LPO x Circa: Daphnis and Chloe. © Laura Manariti.&#xA;Multitudes is an exciting new arts festival taking place at the Southbank Centre from 23 April to 3 May 2025. This festival reimagines the concert hall experience by blending orchestral music with a wide range of artistic disciplines, including dance, performance, spoken word, and visual arts.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
