<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maawura Totoe on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/maawura-totoe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maawura Totoe on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/maawura-totoe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: this week in art (13th- 15th March 2020)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-this-week-in-art-13th-15th-march-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flofavourite-this-week-in-art-13th-15th-march-2020/</guid>
      <description>The Affordable Art Fair Illustration: Affordable Art Fair&#xA;When?&#xA;12th March- 15th March&#xA;Price?&#xA;£9-27&#xA;#FLODown: The spring edition of the Affordable Art Fair lands in Battersea Park this weekend. The fair will feature contemporary artworks priced between £50-£6000 from 100s of galleries from all over the globe. Expect to find a plethora of workshops, talks and tours, plus this will be a fantastic opportunity to get your hands on some great art pieces at affordable prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Women&#39;s Day 2020: the art edition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/international-womens-day-the-art-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/international-womens-day-the-art-edition/</guid>
      <description>Women have long been under-represented in the art world. In 2020 with what appears to be the glass ceiling breaking, we are seeing more exhibitions by women. To mark international women’s day and to commemorate the #5WomenArtists campaign we are sharing some of the exhibitions by female artists you can see in London right now and a couple upcoming exhibitions.&#xA;Dora Maar Exhibition Image: Tate&#xA;When?&#xA;20th November 2019 - 15th March 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick &amp; easy recipes: Kiwi avocado and tomato salad</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/kiwi-avocado-and-tomato-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/kiwi-avocado-and-tomato-salad/</guid>
      <description>Kiwi fruit is full of nutrients such as vitamin C, vitamin K, vitamin E and potassium; plus, they contain a whole host of antioxidants and fibre. People don’t often consider adding kiwi to a salad&amp;hellip; but it’s completely delicious, so here’s a recipe for a quick and easy kiwi, avocado and tomato salad!&#xA;Ingredients Honey – Lime Vinaigrette Dressing&#xA;2 teaspoons of virgin olive oil&#xA;1 ½ tablespoons of fresh lime juice</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
