<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Art1 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/art1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Art1 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/art1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exhibitions not to miss in London this August 2020</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flodown-this-month-in-art-q4wqv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flodown-this-month-in-art-q4wqv/</guid>
      <description>Toyin Ojih Odutola: A Countervailing Theory When: The Barbican&#xA;When: 11 August – 23 August 2020&#xA;**Price:**Free&#xA;Image: Babrican&#xA;**#FLODown:**The Barbican’s art gallery, The Curve, presents the works of Nigerian-American artist Toyin Ojih Odutola. Odutola explores an imagined ancient myth, with an immersive accompanying soundscape by artist Peter Adjaye. Odutola plays with the notion that drawing can be a form of storytelling, and challenges viewers to piece together fragments of the stories she presents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhibitions not to miss in London this September 2020</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/htwjtzletaqacofx88prfpyh4zapsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/htwjtzletaqacofx88prfpyh4zapsr/</guid>
      <description>London Grads Now Where?&#xA;Saatchi Gallery&#xA;When?&#xA;3 September – 25 September 2020&#xA;Price: £3&#xA;Image: MTotoe&#xA;#FLODown: Saatchi Gallery reopens on Thursday 3 September with London Grads Now. The exhibition will bring together the works of over 150 graduating artists from London’s leading fine arts schools includingRoyal College of Art, UCL: Slade School of Art, Goldsmiths: University of London, UAL: Chelsea College of Arts, UAL: Wimbledon College of Arts, UAL: Camberwell College of ArtsandUAL: Central Saint Martins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Nicole Schoeni</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nicole-schoeni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nicole-schoeni/</guid>
      <description>“What I really love to do is to support artists and to be a patron and to share stories.”&#xA;- Nicole Schoeni&#xA;Image: Nicole Schoeni. Schoeni Projects&#xA;Nicole is an experienced gallerist and gallery director, and the founder of Schoeni Projects. She has lived in Hong Kong for most of her life, although attended school and university in the UK. Contemporary and street art are two of her passions, although what she really loves the most about the art world is collaborating with creatives and meeting new people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Women&#39;s Day 2020: the art edition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/international-womens-day-the-art-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/international-womens-day-the-art-edition/</guid>
      <description>Women have long been under-represented in the art world. In 2020 with what appears to be the glass ceiling breaking, we are seeing more exhibitions by women. To mark international women’s day and to commemorate the #5WomenArtists campaign we are sharing some of the exhibitions by female artists you can see in London right now and a couple upcoming exhibitions.&#xA;Dora Maar Exhibition Image: Tate&#xA;When?&#xA;20th November 2019 - 15th March 2020</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
