<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Art10 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/art10/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Art10 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/art10/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>50 art exhibitions to see in London during Frieze Week 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/50-art-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-during-frieze-week-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/50-art-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-during-frieze-week-2024/</guid>
      <description>London’s most anticipated art month is on the horizon, with Frieze London and Masters returning to The Regent’s Park from 9 - 13 October 2024. This renowned week typically sees a flurry of activity across the city, with numerous art fairs, events, and exhibitions showcasing the best in contemporary and historical art. To help you navigate the excitement, here is your guide to 50 art exhibitions not to be missed during Frieze Week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahmed Mater: Chronicles at Christie&#39;s London review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ahmed-mater-chronicles-at-christies-london-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ahmed-mater-chronicles-at-christies-london-review/</guid>
      <description>Christie’s has a wonderful summer treat for us all with their exhibition for the summer featuring Ahmed Mater, a leading Saudi Contemporary Artist. This exhibition, to date, is the most comprehensive dedicated to Ahmed Mater. I have become acutely aware my knowledge of artists from Asia and the Middle East is greatly lacking and I found this free exhibition to be a wonderful introduction which I am sure will propel me to seek out more work of artists from these regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Oskar Zięta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-oskar-zieta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-oskar-zieta/</guid>
      <description>“When you love what you do, you are determined to achieve the intended goal - the creative process becomes a part of you.”&#xA;- Oskar Zięta&#xA;Oskar Zięta&#xA;Oskar Zięta, architect, process designer and artist, works across disciplines to explore the intersections of form, material and technology. His practice combines design, engineering, art and bionics to produce objects that push the limits of metal and its potential. Using a technique he developed called FiDU, Zięta inflates thin steel sheets with air, shaping them into durable, lightweight structures with a strong sculptural presence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: 13th Edition of Sculpture in the City 2024, City of London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/13th-edition-of-sculpture-in-the-city-2024-city-of-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/13th-edition-of-sculpture-in-the-city-2024-city-of-london/</guid>
      <description>We were keen to receive an invitation to tour this year’s 13th Edition of Sculpture in the City. There is something about public sculpture, which is extremely appealing, with each sculpture displayed with its own unique back drop and surroundings and the opportunity of accidental interaction with the art.&#xA;Temple, Richard Mackness, part of the 13th edition of Sculpture in the City. © Richard Mackness. Photo © Nick Turpin.&#xA;Having lived in Sydney for 13 years Sculpture by the Sea (begins mid-October) was one of my favourite events of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Academy Summer Exhibition 2025 review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</guid>
      <description>Arriving right on cue with the first wafts of summer London heat, the Royal Academy Summer Show has returned for its 257th exhibition. Curated under the theme of ‘Dialogues,’ the 2025 edition is coordinated by internationally acclaimed architect and Royal Academician Farshid Moussavi and explores art’s capacity to forge dialogues and build sensitivity towards societal concerns such as ecology, survival and living together. As Moussavi explained: “These dialogues can be between people of different races, genders, or cultures; between humans, all species, and the planet; or across different disciplines - art, science, politics for example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The European art exhibitions worth travelling for in autumn 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-european-art-exhibitions-worth-travelling-for-in-autumn-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-european-art-exhibitions-worth-travelling-for-in-autumn-2024/</guid>
      <description>With several art fairs and art weeks scheduled across Europe this autumn, there are numerous reasons to travel. From delving into Berlin&amp;rsquo;s dynamic 90s scene to attending the Frans Hals exhibition in the same city, and exploring a group exhibition focused on textile storytelling in Amsterdam, there’s much to anticipate. This is your essential guide to the must-see art exhibitions in Paris, Berlin, and Amsterdam this autumn, along with our top recommendations for the pavilions at the 2024 Venice Biennale.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
