<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artlatest on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/artlatest/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artlatest on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/artlatest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Where to find public art in London right now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-public-art-in-london-this-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-to-find-public-art-in-london-this-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>Summer in London offers the perfect opportunity to delve into the city&amp;rsquo;s fantastic public art trails. With the resurgence of public art programmes at The Southbank Centre, alongside the public art trail associated with Chelsea and Kensington Art Week, as well as permanent fixtures like The Line in East London and the last opportunity to view sculptures from the 12th edition of Sculptures in the City, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty to explore. Here&amp;rsquo;s our guide on when and where to experience free public art in London this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A guide to events not to miss at London Craft Week 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/events-not-to-miss-at-london-craft-week-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/events-not-to-miss-at-london-craft-week-2024/</guid>
      <description>London Craft Week 2024 returns this week for its 10th edition, running from 13 - 19 May 2024, highlighting British and international creativity by showcasing over 750 established and emerging makers, designers, brands, and galleries. The festival offers a curated selection of events that promise to inspire and help you discover some of the great talent right on our doorstep! Here are eight notable events to explore during London Craft Week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 unmissable art fairs and events in London for 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/22-unmissable-art-fairs-and-events-in-london-for-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/22-unmissable-art-fairs-and-events-in-london-for-2025/</guid>
      <description>This year, London will host an array of art fairs, art weeks, and design festivals, showcasing everything from photography and contemporary art to ceramics, antiques, sculpture, and innovative design. The 2025 art scene will be as vibrant as ever, featuring long-established events like Frieze, LAPADA, and the London Design Festival, as well as exciting newcomers such as Fresh: Art Fair and the return of the London Design Biennale. With various art weeks, including Clerkenwell Design Week, also on the calendar, here’s a guide to twenty-two unmissable art fairs, events, and festivals in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahmed Mater: Chronicles at Christie&#39;s London review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ahmed-mater-chronicles-at-christies-london-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ahmed-mater-chronicles-at-christies-london-review/</guid>
      <description>Christie’s has a wonderful summer treat for us all with their exhibition for the summer featuring Ahmed Mater, a leading Saudi Contemporary Artist. This exhibition, to date, is the most comprehensive dedicated to Ahmed Mater. I have become acutely aware my knowledge of artists from Asia and the Middle East is greatly lacking and I found this free exhibition to be a wonderful introduction which I am sure will propel me to seek out more work of artists from these regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art exhibitions opening in London in January 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-opening-in-london-in-january-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-opening-in-london-in-january-2024/</guid>
      <description>While January sees the closure of several art exhibitions, it also brings the excitement of new and returning showcases. The Bloomberg New Contemporaries returns to the Camden Arts Centre, Somerset House hosts an exhibition dedicated to &amp;lsquo;cuteness,&amp;rsquo; and the London Art Fair makes its comeback. Here&amp;rsquo;s a sneak peek at the upcoming art exhibitions opening in the city this January. Fresh off the Christmas festivities, what better way to shake off the January blues than by diving into fantastic art experiences?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art exhibitions to watch out for in London in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-to-watch-out-for-in-london-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-to-watch-out-for-in-london-in-2025/</guid>
      <description>Announcements are already rolling in for London’s 2025 art exhibitions, and the line-up is shaping up splendidly. Highlights include the UK’s first exhibition dedicated to José María Velasco, Mexico’s acclaimed 19th-century painter, and the Royal Academy’s Brasil! Brasil! The Birth of Modernism, featuring over 130 works by ten prominent Brazilian artists. The newly opened V&amp;amp;A East Museum will debut The Music Is Black: A British Story, while next year will also bring two major Van Gogh exhibitions—one at the National Gallery and another at the Royal Academy of Arts, where Anselm Kiefer’s work will be shown in dialogue with Van Gogh’s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artists to see at The Other Art Fair London March edition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-other-art-fair-returns-to-truman-brewery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-other-art-fair-returns-to-truman-brewery/</guid>
      <description>The Other Art Fair opened at the Truman Brewery on Thursday evening to heaving crowds of art lovers.&#xA;The Other Art Fair opened at the Truman Brewery on Thursday evening to heaving crowds of art lovers.&#xA;Art should never be elite and here you will find a wonderful variety at accessible prices with the opportunity to meet 100+ artists in person which can only enhance your experience of viewing or purchasing art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canary Wharf’s Winter Lights Festival to return in January 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/canary-wharfs-winter-lights-festival-to-return-january-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/canary-wharfs-winter-lights-festival-to-return-january-2025/</guid>
      <description>London’s dazzling Winter Lights festival returns with 11 new installations and iconic displays, transforming Canary Wharf from 21 January 2025.&#xA;The Clew by Ottotto&#xA;Canary Wharf’s Winter Lights festival returns this January for its ninth edition, bringing with it a blend of light-based art installations from both renowned and emerging artists worldwide. The free, annual event has become a much-anticipated fixture for Londoners and visitors alike, as the neighbourhood is transformed into a vibrant, luminous wonderland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kew Gardens Orchid Festival 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/kew-gardens-orchid-festival-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/kew-gardens-orchid-festival-2024/</guid>
      <description>Kew Gardens 28th annual Orchid Festival has taken over the Princess of Wales Conservatory. Inspiration this year comes from the beauty and biodiversity of Madagascar which is home to over 1,000 species of orchid. We enjoyed leaving the crisp winter air of the gardens and entering the 24C heat to view the 5,000 orchid plants that make up this year’s displays. The flowers cascade over walls, along bridges and are erected into tall towers and arches to spectacular effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pauline Loctin&#39;s ‘Flying in Nuanced Colours’ to debut at Uncommon Holborn for London Design Festival 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pauline-loctin-installation-to-debut-at-uncommon-holborn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pauline-loctin-installation-to-debut-at-uncommon-holborn/</guid>
      <description>Uncommon Holborn to present Pauline Loctin’s ‘Flying in Nuanced Colours’— a major paper sculpture installation for London Design Festival in September.&#xA;Pauline Loctin x Uncommon Holborn. Photo by Mark Cocksedge.&#xA;This September, Uncommon Holborn will host Flying in Nuanced Colours, a striking installation by renowned paper sculptor Pauline Loctin, as part of London Design Festival 2024. The exhibition, a bespoke commission for the B Corp certified workspace provider, merges traditional origami with modern art to create a captivating visual experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photography exhibitions to see in London now and in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/photography-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-now-and-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/photography-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-now-and-in-2025/</guid>
      <description>London is currently hosting an array of photography exhibitions offering compelling reflections on nature, identity, and urban life — with even more set to open in the later stages of 2025. From Wildlife Photographer of the Year at the Natural History Museum, which highlights the beauty and fragility of the natural world, to Gabriel Moses’ exhibition at 180 Studios, showcasing his work across fashion, music, and sport. The Photographers’ Gallery offers a glimpse into the changing landscape of Leeds with a Peter Mitchell retrospective, while Nature Study at the V&amp;amp;A explores ecological themes through the contemporary photobook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Academy of Arts will present an exhibition of Swiss architectural practice Herzog &amp; de Meuron</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-of-arts-will-present-an-exhibition-of-swiss-architectural-practice-herzog-amp-de-meuron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-of-arts-will-present-an-exhibition-of-swiss-architectural-practice-herzog-amp-de-meuron/</guid>
      <description>The Royal Academy of Arts will host an exhibition in July featuring Swiss architectural firm Herzog &amp;amp; de Meuron (H&amp;amp;dM), providing visitors with unprecedented access to the firm&amp;rsquo;s methodology, philosophy, and groundbreaking projects.&#xA;Image: Herzog &amp;amp; de Meuron. Elbphilharmonie Hamburg, 2001-16. Photo © Iwan Baan.&#xA;The Royal Academy of Arts will unveil an eagerly anticipated exhibition of the celebrated Swiss architectural firm Herzog &amp;amp; de Meuron (H&amp;amp;dM), marking the duo&amp;rsquo;s first showcase in London in almost two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Artist’s Garden: the transformation of Temple Station&#39;s roof terrace</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-transformation-of-temple-stations-roof-terrace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-transformation-of-temple-stations-roof-terrace/</guid>
      <description>Holly Hendry&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Slackwater&amp;rsquo; is the latest art installation to appear in the Artist&amp;rsquo;s Garden on the roof of Temple Station.&#xA;Image: Holly Hendry&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Slackwater&amp;rsquo; Artist Roof Garden. July 2023. © MTotoe&#xA;Holly Hendry&amp;rsquo;s art installation, Slackwater, takes centre stage in the Artist&amp;rsquo;s Garden by Temple tube station. The installation features a maze of intricately entangled tubes, constructed with industrial-scale ducting, electricity spools, and inflated boat fenders. Representing the area&amp;rsquo;s watery history and the abstract rhythms of the Thames and the human body, this large-scale sculpture will be on display on the rooftop site until September 2024.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
