<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thescene4 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/thescene4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thescene4 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/thescene4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Much Ado About Nothing, Shakespeare&#39;s Globe Theatre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/much-ado-about-nothing-shakespeares-globe-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/much-ado-about-nothing-shakespeares-globe-review/</guid>
      <description>The Globe’s 2024 summer season is off to a flying start with a joyous romp through one of Shakespeare’s much-loved comedies.&#xA;Ekow Quartey as Benedick and Amalia Vitale as Beatrice. Photography by Marc Brenner.&#xA;Sean Holmes’ production of Much Ado About Nothing is the kind of Shakespeare GCSE English teachers dream about. We are transported to the warm and hazy summer days of sixteenth century Italy, where trees are laden with ripening oranges, noblemen stroll through sun-dappled orchards and evenings are filled with the lively intricacies of dances and music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIANA The Untold and Untrue Story at the King&#39;s Head Theatre review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-the-untold-and-untrue-story-at-the-kings-head-theatre-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-the-untold-and-untrue-story-at-the-kings-head-theatre-review/</guid>
      <description>After a sold-out Edinburgh Fringe run in 2023 and winning the OffFest Award for Best Play, Diana - The Untold and Untrue Story has arrived in London for a three-week run at the King’s Head Theatre in Islington. Let me start by saying it is the best and silliest kind of fun and the most I’ve laughed in such a short space of time. Book it!&#xA;Diana the Untrue and Untold Story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL, Mohamed Jabaly, SAFAR Film Festival</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-life-is-beautiful-mohamed-jabaly-safar-film-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-life-is-beautiful-mohamed-jabaly-safar-film-festival/</guid>
      <description>The opening documentary of this year’s SAFAR Film Festival is a moving, first-person account of Mohamed Jabaly’s experience of travelling abroad and finding himself stranded, unable to return to his home in Gaza, forced to watch war unfold through his phone screen, and the community that forms around him as he fights to remain in a country that considers him stateless.&#xA;Life Is Beautiful.&#xA;Palestine is at the heart of this year’s SAFAR Film Festival, the largest festival in the UK dedicated to cinema from the Arab world.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
