<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Art8 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/art8/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Art8 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/art8/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Art exhibitions opening in London in January 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-opening-in-london-in-january-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-exhibitions-opening-in-london-in-january-2024/</guid>
      <description>While January sees the closure of several art exhibitions, it also brings the excitement of new and returning showcases. The Bloomberg New Contemporaries returns to the Camden Arts Centre, Somerset House hosts an exhibition dedicated to &amp;lsquo;cuteness,&amp;rsquo; and the London Art Fair makes its comeback. Here&amp;rsquo;s a sneak peek at the upcoming art exhibitions opening in the city this January. Fresh off the Christmas festivities, what better way to shake off the January blues than by diving into fantastic art experiences?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kew Gardens Orchid Festival 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/kew-gardens-orchid-festival-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/kew-gardens-orchid-festival-2024/</guid>
      <description>Kew Gardens 28th annual Orchid Festival has taken over the Princess of Wales Conservatory. Inspiration this year comes from the beauty and biodiversity of Madagascar which is home to over 1,000 species of orchid. We enjoyed leaving the crisp winter air of the gardens and entering the 24C heat to view the 5,000 orchid plants that make up this year’s displays. The flowers cascade over walls, along bridges and are erected into tall towers and arches to spectacular effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UVA: Synchronicity at 180 Studios Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/uva-synchronicity-at-180-studios-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/uva-synchronicity-at-180-studios-review/</guid>
      <description>In a city where immersive experiences have become a dime a dozen, with each vying for your hard-earned money, it&amp;rsquo;s no wonder that skepticism often prevails when new offerings hit your inbox. But let us assure you, Synchronicity by UVA at 180 Studios is not one of those exhibitions that leaves you questioning the value of your ticket.&#xA;Image: UVA: Synchronicity at 180 Studios. October 2023. © MTotoe.&#xA;Founded by Matt Clark in 2003, UVA (United Visual Artist) has earned international commissions from prestigious institutions, thanks to their unique blend of light, space, sound, and custom-made kinetic instruments.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
