<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artnews5 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/artnews5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artnews5 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/artnews5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Canary Wharf’s Winter Lights Festival to return in January 2025</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/canary-wharfs-winter-lights-festival-to-return-january-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/canary-wharfs-winter-lights-festival-to-return-january-2025/</guid>
      <description>London’s dazzling Winter Lights festival returns with 11 new installations and iconic displays, transforming Canary Wharf from 21 January 2025.&#xA;The Clew by Ottotto&#xA;Canary Wharf’s Winter Lights festival returns this January for its ninth edition, bringing with it a blend of light-based art installations from both renowned and emerging artists worldwide. The free, annual event has become a much-anticipated fixture for Londoners and visitors alike, as the neighbourhood is transformed into a vibrant, luminous wonderland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jasleen Kaur wins Turner Prize 2024</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/jasleen-kaur-wins-turner-prize-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/jasleen-kaur-wins-turner-prize-2024/</guid>
      <description>Jasleen Kaur wins the 2024 Turner Prize for her exploration of culture, identity, and resilience through sound, music, and everyday objects.&#xA;Turner Prize 2024 Ceremony Tate Britain 3 December 2024 Credit David Parry, PA Media Assignments.&#xA;Jasleen Kaur has been named the winner of the prestigious Turner Prize 2024, earning the £25,000 award. The announcement was made during a live ceremony at Tate Britain, hosted by actor James Norton and broadcast on the BBC News channel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Gallery Van Gogh exhibition to open 24 hours</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/national-gallery-van-gogh-exhibition-to-open-24-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/national-gallery-van-gogh-exhibition-to-open-24-hours/</guid>
      <description>The National Gallery will open overnight on 17 January 2025, for the final weekend of its sell-out exhibition, Van Gogh: Poets and Lovers.&#xA;Vincent van Gogh Sunflowers, 1888; oil on canvas 92.1 × 73 cm, Bought, Courtauld Fund, 1924, © The National Gallery, London.&#xA;As the critically acclaimed Van Gogh: Poets and Lovers exhibition at the National Gallery approaches its final days, the Gallery will open its doors all night on Friday 17 January 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pauline Loctin&#39;s ‘Flying in Nuanced Colours’ to debut at Uncommon Holborn for London Design Festival 2024</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/pauline-loctin-installation-to-debut-at-uncommon-holborn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/pauline-loctin-installation-to-debut-at-uncommon-holborn/</guid>
      <description>Uncommon Holborn to present Pauline Loctin’s ‘Flying in Nuanced Colours’— a major paper sculpture installation for London Design Festival in September.&#xA;Pauline Loctin x Uncommon Holborn. Photo by Mark Cocksedge.&#xA;This September, Uncommon Holborn will host Flying in Nuanced Colours, a striking installation by renowned paper sculptor Pauline Loctin, as part of London Design Festival 2024. The exhibition, a bespoke commission for the B Corp certified workspace provider, merges traditional origami with modern art to create a captivating visual experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W London launches AMPLIFIED: a monthly live music series</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/w-london-launches-amplified-a-montly-live-music-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/w-london-launches-amplified-a-montly-live-music-series/</guid>
      <description>W London brings emerging local and international artists to Soho with exclusive performances at The Perception Bar.&#xA;W AMPLIFIED. Image credit Grant Walker.&#xA;This February, W London unveils AMPLIFIED, an electrifying monthly live music series at The Perception Bar, located inside the iconic hotel in the heart of Soho’s Leicester Square. Curated by DJ and W Music Curator Juss Jak (Jakki Degg), the series celebrates emerging talent from both local and international music scenes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
