<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel Feature on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/travel-feature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel Feature on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/travel-feature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hart Shoreditch Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hart-shoreditch-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/hart-shoreditch-review/</guid>
      <description>Hart Shoreditch, situated in the vibrant heart of Shoreditch, provides a charming and sophisticated retreat that captures the essence of the local area.&#xA;Image: Hart Shoreditch&#xA;Located in the beating heart of Shoerditch, Hart Shoreditch offers a cosy, laid back and elegant base in which to explore all the local area has to offer. Inspired by East London’s past, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique design is a celebration of Shoreditch and its heritage as a centre for craftspeople and makers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 great ideas for enjoying a last-minute holiday in Prague</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/4-great-ideas-for-enjoying-a-last-minute-holiday-in-prague/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/4-great-ideas-for-enjoying-a-last-minute-holiday-in-prague/</guid>
      <description>Discover the charms of spontaneous travel in Prague, where you can enjoy adventures amid its rich culture and scenic beauty.&#xA;Image: Charles Bridge in Prague during sunset. © Jay Ngai&#xA;Tourism in Prague is thriving, which means it&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to visit. The city collaborates with the PCT each year to promote domestic tourism and welcome tourists. According to František Cipro, director of Prague City Tourism (PCT), Prague will welcome nearly eight million visitors in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best art galleries to visit in Stockholm</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/stockholm-travel-guide-the-best-art-galleries-to-visit-in-stockholm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/stockholm-travel-guide-the-best-art-galleries-to-visit-in-stockholm/</guid>
      <description>A visit to Stockholm is incomplete without exploring its thriving art scene, from galleries showcasing Swedish artists to the unique artwork displayed in the city&amp;rsquo;s underground stations. This guide highlights some of the must-visit galleries in Stockholm.&#xA;Click here to discover our guide to museums and places to eat in Stockholm.&#xA;Artipelag The Solar Egg sculpture by Bigert &amp;amp; Bergström. The Solar Egg is part of Sculpture in Nature, Artipelag’s permanent outdoor exhibition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel Athens Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/four-seasons-astir-palace-hotel-athens-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/four-seasons-astir-palace-hotel-athens-review/</guid>
      <description>Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel Athens is a remarkable hotel that offers a luxurious experience and a tranquil and rejuvenating vacation.&#xA;Image: Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel, Athens, March 2023, © MTotoe&#xA;The Four Seasons Astir Palace Hotel is a luxurious seaside escape located on a pine-clad peninsula in the Athenian Riviera, just 30 minutes away from the historical city centre of Athens and the Athens International Airport. With a rich history dating back to 1958, the hotel underwent a €650 million renovation in 2019 and boasts a unique blend of modern luxury and heritage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The European art exhibitions worth travelling for in autumn 2024</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/the-european-art-exhibitions-worth-travelling-for-in-autumn-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/the-european-art-exhibitions-worth-travelling-for-in-autumn-2024/</guid>
      <description>With several art fairs and art weeks scheduled across Europe this autumn, there are numerous reasons to travel. From delving into Berlin&amp;rsquo;s dynamic 90s scene to attending the Frans Hals exhibition in the same city, and exploring a group exhibition focused on textile storytelling in Amsterdam, there’s much to anticipate. This is your essential guide to the must-see art exhibitions in Paris, Berlin, and Amsterdam this autumn, along with our top recommendations for the pavilions at the 2024 Venice Biennale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things to do in the Seychelles</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/things-to-do-in-the-seychelles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/things-to-do-in-the-seychelles/</guid>
      <description>The Seychelles is an island nation made up of 115 islands (you can hop between islands via boat or plane, bear in mind a number of these islands are privately owned). With two UNESCO world heritage sites, the Seychelles also features the most breath-taking views you could ever imagine and is home to some of the most picturesque white sand beaches, delicious food and equally intriguing wildlife.&#xA;Here is our guide to some of the best things to do whilst on this tropical island…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
