<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Art5 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/art5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Art5 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/art5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A group exhibition featuring nine contemporary artists opens at Pictorum Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-group-exhibition-featuring-nine-contemporary-artists-opens-at-pictorum-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-group-exhibition-featuring-nine-contemporary-artists-opens-at-pictorum-gallery/</guid>
      <description>‘Only Until This Cigarette is Ended’, a group exhibition by nine contemporary artists, offers a multifaceted exploration of collective memory and reflection at Pictorum Gallery.&#xA;Image: Only Until This Cigarette is Ended exhibition at Pictorum Gallery. Image courtesy of Pictorum Gallery.&#xA;A group exhibition, Only Until This Cigarette is Ended, has opened at Pictorum Gallery, showcasing the works of nine international artists. Among them are Leily Moghtader Mojdehi, Tosin Kalejaye, Naomi Boiko, Olamide Ogunade, Elena Rivera-Montanes, Verde, Nina Baxter, Johanna Bath, and Brittany Fanning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HENI presents major show by Brian Clarke at Newport Street Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/xxrfdplyfovy752uue5w6pqljfl2yk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/xxrfdplyfovy752uue5w6pqljfl2yk/</guid>
      <description>An exhibition of works by Brian Clarke is coming to Newport Street Gallery in June 2023.&#xA;Image: Brian Clarke, World without End, 2017 Courtesy Brian Clarke Studio&#xA;An exhibition entitled A Great Light featuring works by Brian Clarke, a renowned stained glass artist, will be on display at Damien Hirst’s Newport Street Gallery from 9 June 2023. The exhibition, presented by HENI, will showcase an extraordinary collection of works from 2002 to the present day to celebrate Clarke&amp;rsquo;s 70th year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Péjú Oshin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-pj-oshin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-pj-oshin/</guid>
      <description>“I also felt that my practice was liminal, because it&amp;rsquo;s between this space of architecture, writing, but also curating or education, a multitude of things.”&#xA;- Péjú Oshin&#xA;Image: Péjú Oshin. Photography by Jake Green, courtesy of Gagosian&#xA;Péjú Oshin’s career as a gallery curator was unexpected. After graduating with a degree in architecture, she found herself in the art world through volunteering and working with young people. Péjú&amp;rsquo;s commitment to community work and education led her to become a curator of Young People’s Programmes at Tate, landing her on Forbes 30 Under 30 shortlist for Arts &amp;amp; Culture in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Academy of Arts will present an exhibition of Swiss architectural practice Herzog &amp; de Meuron</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-of-arts-will-present-an-exhibition-of-swiss-architectural-practice-herzog-amp-de-meuron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/royal-academy-of-arts-will-present-an-exhibition-of-swiss-architectural-practice-herzog-amp-de-meuron/</guid>
      <description>The Royal Academy of Arts will host an exhibition in July featuring Swiss architectural firm Herzog &amp;amp; de Meuron (H&amp;amp;dM), providing visitors with unprecedented access to the firm&amp;rsquo;s methodology, philosophy, and groundbreaking projects.&#xA;Image: Herzog &amp;amp; de Meuron. Elbphilharmonie Hamburg, 2001-16. Photo © Iwan Baan.&#xA;The Royal Academy of Arts will unveil an eagerly anticipated exhibition of the celebrated Swiss architectural firm Herzog &amp;amp; de Meuron (H&amp;amp;dM), marking the duo&amp;rsquo;s first showcase in London in almost two decades.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
