<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London17 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london17/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London17 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london17/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lindokuhle Sobekwa wins 2025 Deutsche Börse Photography Foundation Prize</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/lindokuhle-sobekwa-wins-2025-deutsche-brse-photography-foundation-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/lindokuhle-sobekwa-wins-2025-deutsche-brse-photography-foundation-prize/</guid>
      <description>Lindokuhle Sobekwa honoured for powerful tribute to his late sister and a poignant reflection on South Africa’s social history.&#xA;Lindokuhle Sobekwa. The Photographers’ Gallery. Deutsche Börse Photography Foundation Prize 2025. Image credit Heather Shuker.&#xA;South African photographer Lindokuhle Sobekwa has been awarded the 2025 Deutsche Börse Photography Foundation Prize for his personal photobook I carry Her photo with Me. The £30,000 prize, announced on 15 May at The Photographers’ Gallery in London by author and photographer Caleb Azumah Nelson, celebrates the most significant contribution to international contemporary photography over the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover exceptional jazz at Ladbroke Hall this April</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/a-month-of-exceptional-jazz-at-ladbroke-hall-this-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/a-month-of-exceptional-jazz-at-ladbroke-hall-this-april/</guid>
      <description>This April, Ladbroke Hall’s renowned Friday Jazz &amp;amp; Dinner series returns, showcasing an impressive roster of artists at its Sunbeam Theatre. Each evening pairs exceptional live jazz with a carefully crafted menu from the award-winning Pollini restaurant. With tickets priced at £15 for standing and £30 for table seating, the series offers an intimate setting to enjoy world-class music in the heart of West London.&#xA;© Ladbroke Hall&#xA;The month opens on 4 April with saxophonist Alex Garnett, who will be joined by Will Barry (piano), Ferg Ireland (double bass), and Will Cleasby (drums).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photography exhibitions to see in London now and in 2025</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/photography-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-now-and-in-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/photography-exhibitions-to-see-in-london-now-and-in-2025/</guid>
      <description>London is currently hosting an array of photography exhibitions offering compelling reflections on nature, identity, and urban life — with even more set to open in the later stages of 2025. From Wildlife Photographer of the Year at the Natural History Museum, which highlights the beauty and fragility of the natural world, to Gabriel Moses’ exhibition at 180 Studios, showcasing his work across fashion, music, and sport. The Photographers’ Gallery offers a glimpse into the changing landscape of Leeds with a Peter Mitchell retrospective, while Nature Study at the V&amp;amp;A explores ecological themes through the contemporary photobook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: We wear our wheels with pride by Robyn Orlin</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</guid>
      <description>I have arrived at the last of the four Van Cleef &amp;amp; Arpel Dance Reflection evenings I chose to review, and I am now wishing I had the energy and time see every show of this contemporary dance festival. It has been a wonderfully diverse showcase, and it seems I saved the most joyous for last.&#xA;The full title of this piece—WE WEAR OUR WHEELS WITH PRIDE AND SLAP YOUR STREET WITH COLOR&amp;hellip; WE SAID “BONJOUR” TO SATAN IN 1820—is a homage to the rickshaw drivers of Durban by South African choreographer, Robyn Orlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Academy Summer Exhibition 2025 review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</guid>
      <description>Arriving right on cue with the first wafts of summer London heat, the Royal Academy Summer Show has returned for its 257th exhibition. Curated under the theme of ‘Dialogues,’ the 2025 edition is coordinated by internationally acclaimed architect and Royal Academician Farshid Moussavi and explores art’s capacity to forge dialogues and build sensitivity towards societal concerns such as ecology, survival and living together. As Moussavi explained: “These dialogues can be between people of different races, genders, or cultures; between humans, all species, and the planet; or across different disciplines - art, science, politics for example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southbank Centre’s new Festival “Multitudes” to open in April 2025</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/southbank-centres-new-festival-multitudes-to-open-in-april-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/southbank-centres-new-festival-multitudes-to-open-in-april-2025/</guid>
      <description>Multitudes at Southbank Centre will reimagine live music through bold collaborations across dance, theatre, and visual arts.&#xA;LPO x Circa: Daphnis and Chloe. © Laura Manariti.&#xA;Multitudes is an exciting new arts festival taking place at the Southbank Centre from 23 April to 3 May 2025. This festival reimagines the concert hall experience by blending orchestral music with a wide range of artistic disciplines, including dance, performance, spoken word, and visual arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOZI Restaurant Victoria Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</guid>
      <description>TOZI, derived from the affectionate Venetian slang for “a close-knit group of friends,” is the brainchild of an Italian trio that met while opening Shoreditch House under the Soho House Group. In 2013, Chef Maurilio Molteni, fresh from his time as Head Chef at Shoreditch House and developing the menu at Cecconi’s, opened the first TOZI restaurant in London. He was joined by Stefano Meloni and Marco Bullegas as restaurant manager and bar manager, respectively.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
