<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/london/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/london/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>London at home: theatre shows available to stream</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/theatre-shows-available-to-stream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/theatre-shows-available-to-stream/</guid>
      <description>The entertainment industry might be on hold for the moment, but there’s still ways to bring the theatre to your living room. With our guide, you can still enjoy a range of shows while we’re all still in lockdown.&#xA;Shakespeare’s Globe Image: Shakespeare’s Globe&#xA;Between the years of 1592-93, The Globe was closed due to an outbreak of the plague. Although The Globe is currently closed again, fortunately this time around, you can still watch a selection of Shakespeare’s plays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLOFavourite: things to do this weekend in London (14th - 16th February 2020)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/p8na0iut7nq41ap9e60i2yd64m7u53/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/p8na0iut7nq41ap9e60i2yd64m7u53/</guid>
      <description>For the arty ones… Steve McQueen at Tate Steve McQueen exhibition at Tate Modern When?&#xA;13th February – 11th May 2020&#xA;Price: £13&#xA;#FLODown: Tate Modern presents the first major exhibition of Turner Prize-winning artist and Oscar-winning filmmaker Steve McQueen. The exhibition features 14 major works spanning across film, photography and sculpture. The exhibition includes his first film that was shot on a Super 8 camera, Exodus 1992/97, and the more recent End Credits2012–on-going.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best markets in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-markets-in-londonrqmarket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-markets-in-londonrqmarket/</guid>
      <description>The London market is at the epicentre of London life from the avid foodie to the antique collector and fashionistas alike, we all want in on the market scene. There is nothing like a Sunday afternoon trip to the market, here is our guide to the best markets in London.&#xA;Columbia Road Flower Market Columbia Road Flower Market situated in trendy Shoreditch is home to several flower stalls. You’ll find friendly traders selling buckets full of the finest cut flowers, bulbs, herbs and garden fittings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best parks in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-parks-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-parks-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Escaping the hectic streets of London is a necessity for many of us, whether its getting lost in a book, going for a walk, or enjoying a picnic with friends there are several activities on offer in London’s many parks. Here’s our guide to the best London parks and all you need to know when you get there.&#xA;Hyde Park Hyde Park is 350 acres of beauty located in the heart of the city, complete with beautiful man-made serpentine.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
