<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Icwart2 on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/icwart2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Icwart2 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/icwart2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Nimrod Vardi and Claudel Goy, directors of arebyte gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nimrod-vardi-and-claudel-goy-the-directors-of-arebyte-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-nimrod-vardi-and-claudel-goy-the-directors-of-arebyte-gallery/</guid>
      <description>“To us, immersive doesn’t just mean 360° projections or putting on a VR headset. It means telling a story that invites people in, that shifts their perception, and brings them along for the journey.”&#xA;- Nimrod Vardi&#xA;Nimrod Vardi and Claudel Goy, the Directors of arebyte gallery&#xA;Venturing outside the usual Central London art stomping grounds can sometimes feel like an effort. But often, it is really worth it. Case in point for arebyte Gallery, currently based on London City Island (but moving all their programming to Camden soon).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Oskar Zięta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-oskar-zieta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-oskar-zieta/</guid>
      <description>“When you love what you do, you are determined to achieve the intended goal - the creative process becomes a part of you.”&#xA;- Oskar Zięta&#xA;Oskar Zięta&#xA;Oskar Zięta, architect, process designer and artist, works across disciplines to explore the intersections of form, material and technology. His practice combines design, engineering, art and bionics to produce objects that push the limits of metal and its potential. Using a technique he developed called FiDU, Zięta inflates thin steel sheets with air, shaping them into durable, lightweight structures with a strong sculptural presence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Varvara Roza</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-varvara-roza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-varvara-roza/</guid>
      <description>“…I am genuinely committed to the promotion of artists whose work is utterly integral to the landscape of contemporary art, because art, to me, is so much more than an asset class&amp;hellip;”&#xA;- Varvara Roza&#xA;Varvara Roza.&#xA;Working from core values of trust and commitment, Varvara Roza is an increasingly renowned private art advisor and artist representative on the London scene whose verve and passion for bringing leading contemporary artists to the global stage is second to none.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
