<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food3 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/food3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food3 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/food3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Le Cordon Bleu to hold Summer Festival in London in July</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/le-cordon-bleu-to-hold-summer-festival-in-london-in-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/le-cordon-bleu-to-hold-summer-festival-in-london-in-july/</guid>
      <description>Le Cordon Bleu London&amp;rsquo;s Summer Festival 2023 is coming to London in July 2023 and will feature cooking demonstrations, workshops, wine tastings, and guest chef showcases by renowned culinary talents.&#xA;Image: Le Cordon Bleu London&#xA;Le Cordon Bleu London is gearing up for their highly anticipated annual Summer Festival, set to be held at their institute in Bloomsbury. Taking place on 1 July 2023, the festival promises a delightful array of activities to entice culinary enthusiasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FLODown: Pizzeria Mozza</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-pizzeria-mozza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/flodown-pizzeria-mozza/</guid>
      <description>Image: @pizza_diaries_ldn&#xA;It’s been a while since I’ve been on the pizza trail, or rather the pizza-in-actual-establishments trail. I was delighted when @marinagpoloughlin writing a sterling review of a new LA pizzeria in Oxford Circus coincided with my company opening an office nearby. Having excitedly told anyone I’d encountered at the office opening about my desire to try this (whilst letting them know I have a pizza blog), I managed to drag a few colleagues out of the local pubs and into the pizzeria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best restaurants to eat light and wholesome food in London</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/best-restaurants-to-eat-light-and-wholesome-food-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Discover London&amp;rsquo;s top destinations for light, nutritious, and wholesome food with our guide. From the ever-popular vegetarian favourite KIN Cafe to the renowned Maggie Jones&amp;rsquo;s, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a range of options to satisfy your cravings.&#xA;Image: Dan Gold&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a dining experience in London that is both delicious and nutritious, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. Our six restaurant recommendations offer a delightful selection of light, flavourful meals that are not only wholesome but also leave you feeling energised and fully satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegan food is not just for January, it’s for life</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/vegan-food-is-not-just-for-january-its-for-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/vegan-food-is-not-just-for-january-its-for-life/</guid>
      <description>It was both extremely satisfying and hugely depressing to me that January ended on a Sunday this year. It looks lovely in the calendar but meant a long stretch till I could eat some cheese. I think it was actually really motivating to have something to focus on and pour my energy into considering the current lockdown, and I would actually recommend setting yourself a goal like this for the weeks moving forward.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
