<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/flo/</link><description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 23:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/flo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Art Basel Qatar launches new fair format and appoints Wael Shawky as artistic director</title><link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/flo/posts/2025-07-21-second-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 23:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/flo/posts/2025-07-21-second-post/</guid><description>&lt;p>Art Basel has announced the launch of its first-ever fair in Qatar, taking place from 5 to 7 February 2026 at M7 in Doha’s Design District, with preview days on 3 and 4 February. Departing from the usual art fair model of booths, Art Basel Qatar will focus on solo exhibitions by galleries, shaped by individual artistic visions. The fair is designed to create a more meaningful experience for visitors while spotlighting artists and galleries from the Middle East, North Africa, South Asia, and beyond.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>7 unmissable activities for children in London this summer</title><link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/flo/posts/unmissable/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 01:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/flo/posts/unmissable/</guid><description>&lt;p>With the summer holidays underway, there are plenty of brilliant things to do with kids across London. Whether you are after outdoor exploration, creative play, or something educational and hands on, there is lots to choose from. From the much loved UNIQLO Tate Play at Tate Modern, this year created by Monster Chetwynd, to a new Carbon Garden at Kew Gardens, Peppa Pig meet and greet sessions high above the city at Battersea Power Station’s Lift 109, and a brand new interactive exhibition at the Science Museum, here is our guide to seven great activities to do with kids in London this summer.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>