<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artreviews on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/artreviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artreviews on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/artreviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review: We wear our wheels with pride by Robyn Orlin</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/we-wear-our-wheels-with-pride-by-robyn-orlin-review/</guid>
      <description>I have arrived at the last of the four Van Cleef &amp;amp; Arpel Dance Reflection evenings I chose to review, and I am now wishing I had the energy and time see every show of this contemporary dance festival. It has been a wonderfully diverse showcase, and it seems I saved the most joyous for last.&#xA;The full title of this piece—WE WEAR OUR WHEELS WITH PRIDE AND SLAP YOUR STREET WITH COLOR&amp;hellip; WE SAID “BONJOUR” TO SATAN IN 1820—is a homage to the rickshaw drivers of Durban by South African choreographer, Robyn Orlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Academy Summer Exhibition 2025 review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/royal-academy-summer-exhibition-2025-review/</guid>
      <description>Arriving right on cue with the first wafts of summer London heat, the Royal Academy Summer Show has returned for its 257th exhibition. Curated under the theme of ‘Dialogues,’ the 2025 edition is coordinated by internationally acclaimed architect and Royal Academician Farshid Moussavi and explores art’s capacity to forge dialogues and build sensitivity towards societal concerns such as ecology, survival and living together. As Moussavi explained: “These dialogues can be between people of different races, genders, or cultures; between humans, all species, and the planet; or across different disciplines - art, science, politics for example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOZI Restaurant Victoria Review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/tozi-restaurant-victoria-review/</guid>
      <description>TOZI, derived from the affectionate Venetian slang for “a close-knit group of friends,” is the brainchild of an Italian trio that met while opening Shoreditch House under the Soho House Group. In 2013, Chef Maurilio Molteni, fresh from his time as Head Chef at Shoreditch House and developing the menu at Cecconi’s, opened the first TOZI restaurant in London. He was joined by Stefano Meloni and Marco Bullegas as restaurant manager and bar manager, respectively.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
