<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blm on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/blm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blm on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/blm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>In conversation with Dr Zara Benjamin-Laing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-dr-zara-benjamin-laing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interviews/in-conversation-with-dr-zara-benjamin-laing/</guid>
      <description>We had a chat with Dr Zara to discover what a day in the life at Birmingham hospital amid the coronavirus pandemic.&#xA;Key workers have been working tirelessly on the front line throughout our nation’s battle against coronavirus. We caught up with NHS doctor, Zara Benjamin-Laing, to discover how day-to-day life has changed at the hospital she works at amid the current pandemic.&#xA;Image: Zara Benjamin-Laing&#xA;Dr Zara Benjamin-Laing is a Senior House Officer (SHO) currently working in Birmingham.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Lives Matter: anti-racist organisations to support in the UK</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/black-lives-matter-how-you-can-help-w6pvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/black-lives-matter-how-you-can-help-w6pvt/</guid>
      <description>The recent death of George Floyd, Breonna Taylor and Ahmaud Arbery in America has sparked global outrage. Thousands of anti-racism protesters across the world are demanding justice for these individuals, and are highlighting the widespread racial injustices that occur daily. Racial issues are not just unique to the US, this is a global issue that we must all work together to solve.&#xA;Over the coming weeks we will sharing a huge range of resources to help you on your journey to education on this topic, and we have been sharing lots of information on our social media too.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
