<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifestyle Feature on FLO London</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/lifestyle-feature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifestyle Feature on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/lifestyle-feature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Antisemitism 101</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/antisemitism-101-rsfue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/antisemitism-101-rsfue/</guid>
      <description>Antisemitism is horrible. As with any discrimination, it taps into the worst corner of the human psyche – the dark feeling of control which flickers within a person when they abuse another simply because they are different or unfamiliar. Whilst Wiley was enjoying such crude empowerment when he spent over 12 hours last week bombarding social media with his antisemitic posts, Jewish people all over the world including myself were left bruised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLO London x British Vogue 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flo-london-x-british-vogue-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flo-london-x-british-vogue-2022/</guid>
      <description>FLO London features in the June, July and August 2022 issues of British Vogue. As a female-owned business this has been a wonderful opportunity and a chance to showcase our newest collection of Ghanaian wax print products made from Nsubra fabrics.&#xA;“I created FLO London The Shop with the intent of relaying the meanings and beauty of some of the wonderful Ghanaian wax print fabrics I have been in awe of my whole life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why have female leaders been so successful in handling the coronavirus pandemic?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfrsk515mq9798w8cyuh8g8fmvwwi1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfrsk515mq9798w8cyuh8g8fmvwwi1/</guid>
      <description>In the last few weeks, the UK has watched as its European neighbours have started to reopen shops, meet with family members and enjoy some semblance of life before lockdown. Like a naughty child, confined to its room, watching his friends from the window as they play outside, the UK public have become increasingly frustrated.&#xA;Although the outbreak of coronavirus is a global pandemic, nations around the world have responded differently with countries such as Germany and New Zealand having relatively more success compared to the UK, America and Brazil who have experienced the highest death tolls.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
