<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London13 on FLO London</title>
    <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london13/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London13 on FLO London</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <atom:link href="https://davidlorenzana.github.io/tags/london13/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A guide to the most beautiful historic houses to visit in London</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/a-guide-to-the-most-beautiful-historic-homes-to-visit-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/a-guide-to-the-most-beautiful-historic-homes-to-visit-in-london/</guid>
      <description>London boasts an array of remarkable historic homes, each offering a unique glimpse into different eras. From classic Tudor dwellings to elegant Georgian townhouses and residences that provide insights into the Victorian era, there&amp;rsquo;s a diverse selection to explore. Whether you adore exquisite interiors or are intrigued by history and artistic masterpieces, here is our guide to beautiful historic houses to visit in London.&#xA;Sir John Soane&amp;rsquo;s Museum Sir John Soane&amp;rsquo;s Museum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art exhibitions opening in London in January 2024</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/art-exhibitions-opening-in-london-in-january-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/art-exhibitions-opening-in-london-in-january-2024/</guid>
      <description>While January sees the closure of several art exhibitions, it also brings the excitement of new and returning showcases. The Bloomberg New Contemporaries returns to the Camden Arts Centre, Somerset House hosts an exhibition dedicated to &amp;lsquo;cuteness,&amp;rsquo; and the London Art Fair makes its comeback. Here&amp;rsquo;s a sneak peek at the upcoming art exhibitions opening in the city this January. Fresh off the Christmas festivities, what better way to shake off the January blues than by diving into fantastic art experiences?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kew Gardens Orchid Festival 2024</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/kew-gardens-orchid-festival-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/kew-gardens-orchid-festival-2024/</guid>
      <description>Kew Gardens 28th annual Orchid Festival has taken over the Princess of Wales Conservatory. Inspiration this year comes from the beauty and biodiversity of Madagascar which is home to over 1,000 species of orchid. We enjoyed leaving the crisp winter air of the gardens and entering the 24C heat to view the 5,000 orchid plants that make up this year’s displays. The flowers cascade over walls, along bridges and are erected into tall towers and arches to spectacular effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NELKEN a piece by Pina Bausch at Sadler&#39;s Wells review</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/review-nelken-a-piece-by-pina-bausch-at-sadlers-wells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/review-nelken-a-piece-by-pina-bausch-at-sadlers-wells/</guid>
      <description>Appropriately after Valentine’s Day we are sitting above a stage carpeted with 8000 carnations to see NELKEN by Tanztheater Wuppertal Pina Bausch + Terrain Boris Charmatz performing on a stage at the Sadler’s Wells Theatre. This seminal piece debuted in 1982 and hasn’t been seen here since 2005. It returns now with a new generation of dancers and under its new artistic director of 18 months, Boris Charmatz.&#xA;Nelken. © Oliver Look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on in London this week: 12 – 18 February 2024</title>
      <link>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-12-18-february-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidlorenzana.github.io/posts/whats-on-in-london-this-week-12-18-february-2024/</guid>
      <description>Discover our pick of events in London this week: 12 – 18 February 2024.&#xA;Guy Johnston and Britten Sinfonia: The Protecting Veil&#xA;Cellist Guy Johnston collaborates with Britten Sinfonia in a compelling concert featuring works by Tavener, Beethoven, and Bartók. Tavener&amp;rsquo;s The Protecting Veil showcases the cello&amp;rsquo;s emotive qualities, with Johnston&amp;rsquo;s performance reflecting his personal connection with the composer.&#xA;Date: 15 February 2024. Time: 7.30pm. Location: Barbican Centre, Silk Street, London</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
